<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>LiveQA 2017 Aggregated Feed</title>
<link>https://sites.google.com/site/trecliveqa2017/</link>
<description>Aggregated YA questions and medical questions </description>
<lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:57:16 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator>
<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
<item>
<title>[ Dream Interpretation ] Open Question : How can I stop myself from having these dreams?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060619AA4Mqys</link>
<description>This past year I've been having a similar stressful dream. I'm like flying through the universe and it just gets bigger and bigger. It's terrifying to me. And strange because the colors are so vivid and there is incredible detail in it. It scares me because I haven't seen these things before. I don't know how my brain is able to create such vivid scenery. It's so intense.

I want it to stop. What can I do?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060619AA4Mqys</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:01:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Law &amp; Ethics ] Open Question : Are you legally allowed to make pipe bombs?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060635AANiz6w</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060635AANiz6w</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:02:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Corporations ] Open Question : Tell us 3 ways you will deliver world class service to our customers.?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060651AAANiJu</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060651AAANiJu</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : What would you do if you woke up to this face?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060655AAQHhRI</link>
<description>https://s.yimg.com/tr/i/2e36dd47319d4e6f9bc2eb207ab33690_A.jpeg</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060655AAQHhRI</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Wrestling ] Open Question : Will Jon ever come back?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</link>
<description>I just don't think he'll ever come back :(</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ LiveQA2017_Medical_Subtask] FakeMedical Question 1</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=FAKEQIDBLABLABLA</link>
<description>NLM FAQ questions for TREC LiveQA 2017 </description>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=FAKEQIDBLABLABLA</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Friends ] Open Question : I am 21 years old and I have social anxiety !?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060609AA0ekES</link>
<description>I have had anxiety really bad since I was a little kid. In elementary school, I was always sitting alone and I never had any friends. I have never been to a party in my life because it's hard for me to try to talk to new people and get to know people. Now that I am older, I know it is important to socialize with people for networking and things. I am a college student and I just don't know how to get over this anxiety that I have. Stepping out of my comfort zone has always scared me. Whenever someone wants to hang out with me , I would just not respond or just make up an excuse as to why I can't hang out with them... There are 2 people that I can hang out with that I do not have anxiety with but one of them has a boyfriend and the other is busy doing other things. We do hang out sometimes. It is just hard for me to get involved with the general public and socialize. I am afraid I'll have panic attacks and I get really offended easily by some people and the things they might say even if it's not meant to be offensive, I get very defensive. I would rather just stay in the house to myself without having to deal with the outside world. What should I do with myself?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060609AA0ekES</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:07:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What's the worst insult you've ever received?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060558AAN61PH</link>
<description>by who?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060558AAN61PH</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : If someone is afraid of losing a best friend, would that be a part of low self esteem?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060554AA1MAAl</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060554AA1MAAl</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:09:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Do you think overweight people are ugly?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060534AAL6Zi9</link>
<description>Just wondering cause my friend's boyfriend just broke up with her and I asked him why and he said it was because she was fat. It really pissed me off, cause she is such an amazing person and they were together for 1 year too!</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060534AAL6Zi9</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:10:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Fashion &amp; Accessories ] Open Question : Best way to sale hundreds of used men's clothing items?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</link>
<description>T-shirts , jeans and shorts . They are like ten plus years old.

The clothing articles are too nice to just give away for free to the Goodwilll.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Other - Cultures &amp; Groups ] Open Question : Do you consider a child with a Black mom and a dad that s mixed with White and Black (50/50) mixed?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060522AAsO9ey</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060522AAsO9ey</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:12:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : Are you happy with the way you look? why or why not?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AAbmLuw</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AAbmLuw</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:13:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : You're winner?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AA4Vru8</link>
<description>~AVGN (big rigs over the road racing)</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AA4Vru8</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:04:55 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Friends ] Open Question : Does this mean he doesn't want me to have male friends?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060431AA91P4n</link>
<description>Does this mean he doesn't want me to have male friends? I was telling him about the girl who was mean to me at school I said "the teacher asked me a question and she (the girl) said 'you talk to him but not me?'" He said "who is him?" Him was the teacher. He never asks "who is her/she" when I mention female friends.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060431AA91P4n</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:14:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : GUYS: What do you find attractive in a girl?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060403AAjbKVK</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060403AAjbKVK</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:15:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Diet &amp; Fitness ] Open Question : One side of my jaw is bigger than the other. Can i reduce it?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</link>
<description>I've noticed that my right jaw muscle is bigger than my left. Is there any way i can reduce it and even it out? I've been chewing on the left side of my mouth for months not but it hasn't been so effective.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ United States ] Open Question : How much can I make with a dependent in tax return while making $10000?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060320AAczlD4</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060320AAczlD4</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:17:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Yahoo Answers ] Open Question : Why does Yahoo Answers select a default category for the questions?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060311AAA5iz5</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060311AAA5iz5</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:18:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Comics &amp; Animation ] Open Question : What anime series should I watch?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060309AARoMVm</link>
<description>I've seen Naruto (+Shipuudden), Code Geass, The Future Diary, Ergo Proxy, Bleach, Steins;Gate, One Punch Man, Sword Art Online, Boruto, My Hero Academia and Death Note. What would you think I would be interested in? Or you can introduce me to a series that you liked</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060309AARoMVm</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:19:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Family ] Open Question : Hi everyone. So I turned 18 back in April (I'm a guy, by the way) and I still live at the house with my legal guardians (grandparents).?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060150AAxqQ4g</link>
<description>I'm going to college next month, but I've got issues here: a) They always complain about me not helping to pay for anything, yet they don't want me to have a job as they say I need to wait for my education to be finished first, b) They continue to try and force their Christianity on me when I've asked nicely for it to stop, and I've refused to participate in any church matters, and c) They promised me I would have my freedom when I turned 18, but here I stand today, still waiting for it. They want to control what music I listen to, what clothes I wear and when I wear them, where I go and when I go and who I go with. My parents are divorced and have other kids, and I can't stay with them, and can't afford to live on campus. So, my question is: What can I do? I'm losing my damn mind here!</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060150AAxqQ4g</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:20:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What are high heels good for?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060148AAdsQv3</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060148AAdsQv3</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:21:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Religion &amp; Spirituality ] Open Question : Why did God resort to killing the Egyptian firstborn, but only the firstborn of Egypt (Exodus 12:29)?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060119AADb3gV</link>
<description>(1) Since Pharaoh hardened his heart and refused to allow the Israelites to go out of Egypt - He ignored God's every warning to let his people go out of Egypt in regards to the previous 9 plagues (Exodus 7-12).

(2) God would be unjust if he had not punished the Egyptians in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22 - The doctrine of eye for eye is due process, which requires the punishment to fit the nature of the crime (Exodus 21:24).

(3) Although the Egyptians were all guilty of genocide (Exodus 12:29) God had no choice but to exercise restraint by killing only the firstborn of Egypt - Which was due process in retaliation for the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22 - l'est all hell should break loose and Pharaoh would've lost any semblance of restraint in his dealings with the Israelites - So it was a matter of expedience that God was restrained in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22.


So, now do you see why God resorted to killing the Egyptian firstborn, whilst exercising restraint in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060119AADb3gV</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:22:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Maintenance &amp; Repairs ] Open Question : Radiator hose hot suspicious leaking?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060023AAbfOtd</link>
<description>Radiator is having behavior problems with this texas 100 degree heat.First yesterday i found there to be barely any coolant and the worst part was the over flow resevoire was extremely bad spraying anti freeze all over the battery. the level on the reservoir read (MIN).Today i drove it and it was spraying pretty damn bad but tonight i put a ton of anti freeze and the spraying has stopped i have not drove the truck but let it idle and heat up and all seem fine BUT there is leaking from something the passenger tire was very wet and i felt around the radiator and the radiator has a very strong heat AROUND THE RADIATOR HOSE.I also discovered STEEL HOSE LINE PREETY WET AND NOT LEAKING BUT PREETY DAMN WET for me not driving it for a few days.and i think the steel hose goes to radiator.As far as the major leak from somewhere that leaks on my tire i cannot really pin point other thinking its either a hose or the radiator but the radiator doesn't have significant bleeding i men its wet but it stops making me think its my own mess from pouring the anti freeze.

OH WELL I GUESS IN THE MORNING I WILL FIND A PUDDLE.

Picture below shows steel hose thats not dripping but WET.(top hose) FOUND MAJOR LEAK went on tire on passenger side seems the resevoir hose to the radiator is disconnected pouring out much anti freeze.So i guess what happened was hose poured out my anti freeze and I'm not sure why yesterday anti freeze started spraying out like crazy maybe its because the radiator had no anti freeze while i was driving thus making engine extremely hot.Im lucky i didn't ruin anything but i will find out tomorrow i doubt any damage.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060023AAbfOtd</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:23:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Why do they Make Porn?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060000AAnqUUF</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060000AAnqUUF</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:24:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Feeling like my friend is fake and doesn't want me around?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055952AAdkgCX</link>
<description>I don't know how to feel about her. We've been friends for almost a year now, she was like so nice at first, she would talk to me everyday, check on me, make sure to see if I was okay, call me , video chat with me, she even promised she'd always be here for me, like real friends do. Now let me tell you, we aren't the most popular kids around and she hasn't been acting herself lately, I feel almost as if she's trying to change herself to fit in with the crowd, I noticed she's been avoiding me lately, she always saying bye and saying she has to go somewhere when ik for sure  that isn't true because she didn't leave this much when we use to be close. I asked her why she always leaving and she said because she wanted to hang with her other friends, that 'we aren't that close" and she doesn't want to talk to me . That really pissed me off because I was like her FIRST friend, i helped her with so many things , I always had her back through thick and thin and all of sudden were not close?? I soon found out that she has a boyfriend, she's been making excuses and saying that she can't talk to me because she's on the phone with her boyfriend or that she's going to see a movie with her boyfriend which  I feel is total lie. I get that she may be busy, but I don't think she's that busy to the point we only talk for 10 seconds now. What do I do?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055952AAdkgCX</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:25:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Religion &amp; Spirituality ] Open Question : Christians now that yahoo answers is broken can you be honest?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055944AAQVhxN</link>
<description>On some level you know that Jesus is made up, why not admit it?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055944AAQVhxN</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:26:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What's your favorite type of allergy medicine?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055928AA41GNB</link>
<description>Also, do you like watching paint dry?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055928AA41GNB</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:59:28 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Pregnancy ] Open Question : Could I be pregnant?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055906AAFwRTR</link>
<description>Me and my bf had sex 3 days before my period, the condom broke and he immediately pulled out. I was supposed to start my period on Friday (7/14) and I started taking my birth control pills on Sunday (7/16). I m now 3 days late for my period.. Could I be pregnant?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055906AAFwRTR</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 08:59:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Mythology &amp; Folklore ] Open Question : Trump told White House staffers to lawyer up, but that Trump's not paying for it. Then he used campaign donations to hire lawyer's for Jr.?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055850AAVtuDn</link>
<description>Is this part of why staffers keep leaking information? Because they know Trump will break the law, but will never help his staff? http://www.politico.com/story/2017/07/15/trump-campaign-paid-jr-attorney-240592 It is proven / public record.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055850AAVtuDn</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 09:58:50 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Politics ] Open Question : Remember when Trump kicked the @sses of 16 Establishment Republicans, then turned around and kicked Hillary and Obama's @sses too?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055840AAGbqdE</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055840AAGbqdE</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 10:58:40 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Biology ] Open Question : Question about height?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055832AAgDfbd</link>
<description>Hi
So my dad is 6'3 and my mom is 5'8. Currently I am 5'6 and I want to stay like that (I'm 15 and a male) (I am also gay and wanna be the sort of "small cute" one in the relationship.) I have been using those subliminals on YouTube to stop growing and they are working. However I don't want my parents to know that I've been doing that because they want me to be tall and they'd be mad if I was purposely staying short. They would probs take me to a doctor and ask why I'm not growing taller, and would the doctor be able to tell I've been using subliminals because my parents would get mad if they knew. Anyone know what kind of answer he would give my parents? Would he say stuff about genetics or would he know I've been purposely staying short. BTW for those of you who don't know subliminals are like messages that can make your brain do stuff to ur body like grow taller, shorter, smaller nose etc.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055832AAgDfbd</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 11:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ User Profiles ] Open Question : 4-12 alphanumerical usernames?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055833AA49BUd</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055833AA49BUd</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 12:58:33 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Other - Beauty &amp; Style ] Open Question : Do you think I could be a foreign host?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055829AA5Rk6s</link>
<description>I'm a young guy who's barely in my twenties, and I was thinking of learning Japanese, and to start living my life in Japan once I'm fluent. To begin my dreams of living in Japan, I thought about starting off as a host at a host club. In Japan, it's not uncommon for Japanese women to pay guys huge sums of money for a couple of cocktails and a few hours of platonic companionship. The key is to be attractive, and to lure in women. I think I have an advantage because I'm foreign. However, to be honest, I'm not the greatest at picking up women because I'm introverted, but I could still make it possible for women to enjoy my presence, since I never had trouble in that area. A description about myself, I'm half French and half Mexican, so I have black hair, but somewhat tanned skin (hazel eyes). I have a swimmer's built, and quite skinny, but I have good muscular definition. I have a youthful face, so I look younger than my real age. As for my overall appearance towards women, I have had two or three random women come to my job just to see me in the past. Anyways, it's not an ideal job (hosting and all), but I think it's better than the other typical jobs as a foreigner (like teaching English to a classroom full of people).</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055829AA5Rk6s</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 13:58:29 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Diet &amp; Fitness ] Open Question : When to have your first cheat meal?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AAuiE3h</link>
<description>So I started a diet + workout, and I am planning to have my cheat meal after total of 10 days of diet and working out

is this OK?

When do people usually have the first cheat meal?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AAuiE3h</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 14:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ User Profiles ] Open Question : 4-12alphanumeric usernames?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AANJUAt</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AANJUAt</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 15:58:00 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : What is wrong with me?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055755AA2Wj64</link>
<description>My friend started dating this guy . Her and the guy met through me. So they have been dating for about 7 months now and she is really happy. I am very happy for her because she deserves to be happy. Most of the time if my friends start dating a guy it seems like we don t really hang out as much anymore, they are always with that person. When I want to hang out with them, they usually bring the guy along. I am happy that she is happy but i don t understand myself because I start feeling lonely and depressed because I have never actually been in a relationship so idk if it s just me or if I m just exaggerating. I love my friends so much and maybe I would understand if I had someone of my own (too bad no one wants me because I look like a whale) but I just miss when boys were not in the picture. I feel like I am maybe exaggerating or maybe I should find new friends who are not thinking about guys or a relationship. I just wish I had someone to talk to about how I have been feeling.....</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055755AA2Wj64</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 16:57:55 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Military ] Open Question : During emergency why people lose all sense? Women and men keep screaming, it doesn't help the situation? Do military personnel panic?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055704AAbYfAv</link>
<description>I mean military personnel practice and trained for such scenario right? So when such things happen they can keep their mind calm and do better action and judgement which mean far more chance of survival. Do you think it's military training exercise that help them or some people are born with such survival mind?

Thank you very much</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055704AAbYfAv</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 17:57:04 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Men's Health ] Open Question : I've had an 8 hour erection?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055620AAvZU0i</link>
<description>It hurts like a b*tch. I saw my wife from behind earlier, for only a second mind you, and it was enough to set me off. She tried to off me later, but it was painful to do even that, and it hurts like a motherf*cker. I'm 18 by the way, so I don't know why I'm having this. It's not like I'm an old d*ck with erectile dysfunction. I should note that my wife and I have been married since last October, and we've gone at it almost every night since. Max Hoopla. Read the description. My wife set me off, and I was up for almost 10 straight hours. After she offed me (which was, for the first time ever, painful), it hurt even worse. It was after I was up for 10 minutes, but after she did that, I was up for another 9 hours and 26 minutes. Not even joking. 

I'm all right now, and my wife and I are planning on taking a couple nights off- and then I'm bedding her like never before. Friday's gonna rock.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055620AAvZU0i</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 18:56:20 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Politics ] Open Question : Are Trump donors ok that when they're donating to his re-election campaign, some of that money is going to lawyer's for Trump Jr.'s defence?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055546AA9Ogmz</link>
<description>Why can't the billionaire's son pay for his own lawyer's instead of using campaign donations?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055546AA9Ogmz</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 19:55:46 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Other - Careers &amp; Employment ] Open Question : Should I quit my two part time jobs for a full time job that pays 14 an hour?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055544AAmrYTk</link>
<description>Okay so I currently have two jobs. One pays 10:50 an hour and I do 30 hours a week with them and my other job pays 11 an hour along with 35-39 hours a week. 

working both I don't get enough sleep. I feel tired and exhausted all of the time and i told myself once I find a normal job id quit both. But the job would have to pay more.

Should I quit both jobs for this one? Its full time so im assuming it would be 40 hours a week</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055544AAmrYTk</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 20:55:44 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : Agree or disagree: introverted usually refers to shy people while extroverted usually describes people who are not shy?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055515AAW2YBD</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055515AAW2YBD</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 21:55:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<!-- UP TO HERE -->
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : I wanna hear you guys most interesting conspiracy theories.. fire away?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055421AAPXE8g</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055421AAPXE8g</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:54:21 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Mathematics ] Open Question : Can anyone help me with this math problem?
I have a question about it.?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055353AAOrVav</link>
<description>http://imgur.com/a/i3dPk

How did 10x-16=-(2x+13) happen?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055353AAOrVav</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:53:53 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Comics &amp; Animation ] Open Question : Who was the fat kid (non ninja?) that died in a Naruto movie. He was giving I think Naruto a piggy back ride and got shuriken to the stomach?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055346AAVFkQZ</link>
<description>I think he was giving Naruto or some other character a piggy back charging towards an enemy. He got shuriken. In the knees or the stomach. I can t remember who it was but it was sad because I think he just wanted to be a ninja or something. I didn t watch Naruto back then and he struck my mind today.</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055346AAVFkQZ</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:53:46 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What if you found out your daughter and son (both 16,17) were having sex with people ? Would you be mad?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055315AAC0IeJ</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055315AAC0IeJ</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:53:15 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Mathematics ] Open Question : Calculus help?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055303AAOrWBG</link>
<description>find the exact length of the curve 

x= t sint y= t cost  0&#8804; t &#8804;1</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055303AAOrWBG</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:53:03 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Higher Education (University +) ] Open Question : What should I major and minor in?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055242AAVm8tk</link>
<description>I want to do something within the law enforcement, either a detective, a CSI, or an emergency dispatcher. Should I major in Biology and minor in criminal justice or major in criminal justice and minor in biology?</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055242AAVm8tk</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:52:42 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Programming &amp; Design ] Open Question : What is your top WordPress plugin that you use for a fresh WP install?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055206AAbEurT</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055206AAbEurT</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:52:06 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Movies ] Open Question : Your favorite over the top action movie!?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055156AAwQf7Q</link>
<description>
</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055156AAwQf7Q</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:51:56 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
<item>
<title>[ Books &amp; Authors ] Open Question : Mystery story ideas?</title>
<link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</link>
<description>wow okay so i've been trying to create a detective webcomic with my friend since new years eve 2015

we haven't done anything for it since then because we could never come up with any ideas

we'd really appreciate some ideas, maybe abducting or homicide 

i dont know if this would help with anything, but its taking place in minneapolis, MN

 the two main characters are detective partners. ones a snarky 24 y/o vietnamese man and the other is an effeminate 23y/o american man and they're close childhood friends??????????

idk this might not be helpful but just in case.

10 points to best answer ;___;</description>
<guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</guid>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:56 GMT</pubDate>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>