<?xml version="1.0" encoding="iso-8859-1"?>
<rss version="2.0"><channel><title>LiveQA 2017 Aggregated Feed</title><link>https://sites.google.com/site/trecliveqa2017/</link><description>Aggregated YA questions and medical questions </description><lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 19:44:18 GMT</lastBuildDate><generator>PyRSS2Gen-1.1.0</generator><docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs><item><title>Question: Help me identify these bugs in my house.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706082608AAOZyMm</link><description>I have all these tiny, brown, hard shell looking bugs in my house.  They look like they are split down the middle but I have not caught one of them flying. We have only noticed them these last two summers and my dad seems to think they are caused by a giant weed that looks like s tree growing right up against my house we just haven't had the chance to remove it. Most of them are located right between the wooden door frame and the door which happens to be located right behind the plant. They are found mostly on the walls and ceiling. I've looked up photos of bedbugs hoping that is not what they are and it seems to look like they aren't. Bedbugs have a redish tint to them while these bugs are dark brown/black. Please help me, I have told my dad that we should call pest control but he wants to solve it on his own. I have not been able to take a photo of them this year because my main concern was trying to get rid of them but I have a photo I sent to my dad last summer but it may not let me post it.  Thank you for any information in advance!!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706082608AAOZyMm</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 09:26:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Judging from my characters names can you guess what time period they live in?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010205AASWV7x</link><description>Genevieve
Edmund
Westleigh
Gjuzel
Bette
Armand
Ruslana
Arabell</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010205AASWV7x</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:02:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How about doing businesse with the guangzhou china versse pu leather bag factory ?about women fashion handbag wholesale.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012014AARkgna</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012014AARkgna</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:20:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can guys wear makeup?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215228AA4URcp</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215228AA4URcp</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: If a store&#8217;s detention pond is broke and they refuse to fix it, what can I do? It is causing flooding to my property.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215427AAsVXdD</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215427AAsVXdD</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:54:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I need to learn how to dance with flexiblity. I would do it at home. like an on line class? I have no dance skill or flexiblity.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706220907AArVCzq</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706220907AArVCzq</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:09:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My bathroom doesn't have a GFCI outlet...can I fix it with an adapter?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221015AAO0TFA</link><description>I'm trying to install an electric bidet in a bathroom that doesn't have a GFCI outlet. Can I use an adapter, such as the TRC 90033, and be just as safe as if I had a regular GFCI outlet? Thanks!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221015AAO0TFA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:10:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What rabbit should I get?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221019AAC0dUP</link><description>My mothers friend has a rabbit she said she would give me, he's a 4 year old lion head boy who's pretty sweet but there are a few things I dislike about him, I didn't really want a buck, and I also think he's a little big for me, as well as that he's not a baby which overall is what I wanted to start out with. 

2. I can buy from a very nice lady I know for a fee of $100 for a lop who is very sweet, I can get a buck or a doe, but I'd have to deal with puberty and the $100 fee instead of free, but I get my baby that I wanted and a lop that I also wanted, help???</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221019AAC0dUP</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:10:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a 6 channel mixer with built in amplifier which I transport. A bit of rain water fell into input?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221154AAaG3wQ</link><description>I have a 6 channel mixer with built in amplifier which I transport. A bit of rain water fell into the input of channel number 2 and later that day the input had a green puffy coating. I scraped it off and thought it would end. I checked it again one week later and all the screws and the input of the channel next to it was puffy and green as well and has made the paint of the amp peel off, and when the paint came off there was a white milky liquid that was underneath. That channel has stopped working completely. I dont know whats going on and I dont know how to prevent whatever this is from spreading. Can someone please help me</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221154AAaG3wQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:11:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is Natural Balance vegetarian food good for the diabectic dog?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221206AAQn4GW</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221206AAQn4GW</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:12:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is exterior latex paint the best paint to paint your house? Or, is oil based paint better? Is either self priming? Or, do I need to prime?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221316AAMiXvq</link><description>My house has a fading 30 year old finish of Cabot's Semi Transparent Oil Based Stain. My home exterior is redwood clapboard.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221316AAMiXvq</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What ship took Amelia Earhart plane from california to hawaii?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221321AACt1Bw</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221321AACt1Bw</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are most girls capabe of getting a flat stomach or is it rare?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221458AAZ04b0</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221458AAZ04b0</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:14:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do cats destroy all the furniture?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221652AAVkBHT</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221652AAVkBHT</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:16:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I was eating hershey's milk chocolate and my pet chicken came in and pecked a piece off. it was about the size of a dime. will she be okay?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221720AAReeMf</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221720AAReeMf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:17:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should I get a bunny?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221831AAjLzFi</link><description>My friend has baby bunnies and I want to get one but I want to know if I would be a good fit. I'm soon to be 18 and still in high school and going to live with my patents until after college (Gonna be a vet tech). I've had rabbits before when I was younger but none for a few years. I would get a cage for it to go in when I'm not not (for school or work) and night but when I'm home it would be able to run around in the "fence" I would buy. I would make sure it had at least two hours a day of being able to run around. I also have two dogs and a cat but the dogs would never be alone with it even when it's in the cage. No small children in the house. We're all over 13 and I would do my research to make sure it had the proper food and toys and such but I just want to know if it would be okay with being in the cage. It would be given attention and I'd litter train it. Also would get it fixed when the times comes. Would it be okay? Thanks!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706221831AAjLzFi</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:18:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is a good 5k time for a 14 year old girl?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222159AA5Izyt</link><description>I just ran my first "5k" at the gym on the elliptical. I finished the 5k distance at 28 minutes. Like I said before, I never ran one before and I'm not sure if that's good or not. What is a good time for a 5k for my age and sex after running for the first time and after practicing/training.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222159AA5Izyt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:21:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can my Chihuahua male and my Papillon female breed? I Know dumb question but I would just like to Know?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222238AAfk43r</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222238AAfk43r</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:22:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does eyeliner clog pores ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222605AA0gsF8</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222605AA0gsF8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:26:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does eyeliner clog pores ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222612AA654T9</link><description>If applied daily?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222612AA654T9</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:26:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Taurus 738 .380 is it worth the buy?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222727AAL5thd</link><description>Im looking for an edc gun, my glock 22 is a little to big, i have heard good and bad things about taurus bit i was wondering if anyone has handled and shot the 738, maybe this little gun is different than other "junk" Taurus ive heard of</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222727AAL5thd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:27:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is there any way to quicken and thicken beard growth?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222855AAcDnrY</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706222855AAcDnrY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:28:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How did the Mandan Indians influence other Indians and Europeans? (Essay Style)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223358AABiOJr</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223358AABiOJr</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:33:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: In Miami dade what color fog lights can you have?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223429AAFfOwx</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223429AAFfOwx</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:34:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: If you were an nfl owner, and you had to hire a current nfl head coach, who would it be? Bill Belichick and Pete Carroll are already taken.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223501AASFZA5</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223501AASFZA5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do I need a permit to get a pellet gun?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223518AAc1wPR</link><description>I plan on starting to raise meat rabbits and to dispatch them I plan on using a pellet gun. Also what would be a good pellet gun to get the job done quickly?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223518AAc1wPR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:35:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: OK writers, should I double space my story?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223749AALs3JX</link><description>I'm working on a story, I want to submit to a magazine called "The First Line". They don't say anything, in  their guidelines, about spacing. Should I double space my story? In addition how should I describe, if at all, the closing procedure for a convenience store?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223749AALs3JX</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:37:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Tattoo forum?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223913AAYJvAX</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223913AAYJvAX</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:39:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Tattoo forum?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223922AAuzA0g</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223922AAuzA0g</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:39:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it a good idea to grow a banana tree in Vegas?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223926AAwqQ5g</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706223926AAwqQ5g</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:39:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it animal abuse if I ignore my kitten when it meows at me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706224201AAAOkRu</link><description>Like if I don't feel like being bothered with him and I go into another room when he's meowing at me is that animal abuse?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706224201AAAOkRu</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:42:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is this a trilby or a fedora
http://imgur.com/AIK09SR?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201942AANqKYN</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201942AANqKYN</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:19:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What do you all think of this burberry messenger bag?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202725AAgXEYl</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202725AAgXEYl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:27:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I drive from CT to the Statue of Liberty without New York City traffic?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202827AAlI2NC</link><description>We are on a road trip from the Midwest and heading to Philadelphia, but wanted to just see the Statue of Liberty.  Is it possible to drive in or will I be victim to the traffic I see in movies?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202827AAlI2NC</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:28:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does this look normal?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202838AAQHizN</link><description>I don't think it looks normal because I always see people hair coming down to their ears but my never do. I have tried 5 different barbers and this is what it always looks like.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706202838AAQHizN</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:28:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I drive from CT to the Statue of Liberty without hitting the heavy NYC traffic?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706203007AAiFsAC</link><description>Obviously I realize it's on an island.  I am merely asking if it is possible to get to the park without driving through the city traffic?  Stay on an interstate for the most part?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706203007AAiFsAC</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How long should socks last?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706203507AAabGyB</link><description>Mine always get holes in them within a weeks worth of wear or less. How long should they last and can i return them if they get holes so soon?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706203507AAabGyB</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:35:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Besides money, what's the point of the Church Of Scientology converting people?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706204417AA6wwYf</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706204417AA6wwYf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:44:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How are you celebrating the 35th anniversary of Canada getting its constitution patriated by the British in 1982?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706204504AAycAwK</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706204504AAycAwK</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:45:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it normal if my kitty is attracted to boobs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706205126AAKCLg5</link><description>so i was laying on my bed without clothes on and she just jumped on the bed and started playing with my boob which i thought was funny and then she tried nibbling on it lol so i had to stop her cause that's weird, but is this normal?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706205126AAKCLg5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:51:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My dog keeps nipping certain family member.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706205934AAW9qdR</link><description>How can I correct this? I have a one year old Australian Shepherd that keeps nipping and biting my step brother and only him, we do not know why she doesn t like him but she acts like she doesn t trust him or something. I could really use advice because I have to stop this behavior because I m worried she might one day really bite him hard and that would be very bad.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706205934AAW9qdR</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:59:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will a robber take the time to take out a gun that is on a locked racked that is bolted to a stud ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706210326AAN16B2</link><description>I mean I can't get it out . I'm a 289 lb male and I can grab it while leaning back and barley hear a creak</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706210326AAN16B2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Groomer cut dogs lip?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211236AAbBBNd</link><description>My groomer cut my dogs lip. Probably an accident. Any ideas on how to care for it. It s still bleeding and he won t let antibiotic stay up there. It s a circular wound less than a cm.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211236AAbBBNd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does this outfit look good? Be honest.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211634AAqr86J</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211634AAqr86J</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:16:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hair oil for stretched ears?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211817AAvChqU</link><description>So I went out and bought coconut oil to stretch my ears. Didn t really read much of the label but I got home and found out its coconut oil for your hair. Can I still use it?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706211817AAvChqU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:18:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are my pants appropriate or too casual?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212019AAwecVE</link><description>I'm starting a new job soon and even though they gave me dress instructions, I'm still confused.  I have these black pants from Nautica (see link) and want to know if they will be appropriate.  The following is an excerpt from the dress code:

"'business-appropriate' clothing is acceptableand encouraged. For men, such clothing includes collared-dress shirts, khaki-type slacks, closed-toe shoes, and socks.  Unacceptable attire includes denim, sports logo wear, athletic or 'athleisure' clothing such as leggings, golf/polo shirts, capri pants, sandals, miniskirts, or other revealing clothing."

I'm concerned the rivets and pockets of these pants might not fit the criteria.  However, I think when I wear a nice button down shirt, belt, and dress shoes it will look good.  Please help.

http://www.nautica.com/slim-fit-stretch-5-pocket-pant/PR7120.html?dwvar_PR7120_color=085#uuid=0f8f81102055ef6157ea01e68a</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212019AAwecVE</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:20:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I buy cup noodles and instant rice in convenience stores in Athens, Greece?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212021AAdeDXv</link><description>I m going to Athens for a few days and was wondering if they have cup noodles instant rice at convenience store and supermarkets. If so how much?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212021AAdeDXv</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:20:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What can my hair have?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212217AATUPSm</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212217AATUPSm</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:22:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I found a new box of e.l.f Hydrating Face Primer torn &amp; the bottle destroyed. I think my dog ate the primer. 14mL bottle. Will he be okay?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212456AAXyFzz</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212456AAXyFzz</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:24:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do some players not have their last names on their kits?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212513AAolmU7</link><description>Ive noticed this for a long time that some players (usually notable) don t use their last names on their soccer kits. Ive never really noticed it in other sports. For example Xavier Hernandez s kit said "Xavi" and Neymar s is "Neymar Jr."Also Aguero s kid says "Kun Aguero" And Sergio Busquetes kit has his first name "Sergio." Does anyone know why these are allowed and players don t have to use their last names?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212513AAolmU7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:25:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where can i buy orange cats in San Francisco?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212832AAADIk7</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212832AAADIk7</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:28:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a dual action otf knife and it seems like the spring is really weak it wont deploy if its upright is there a way to fix this?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212934AAcc7Fx</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706212934AAcc7Fx</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:29:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Was a fish named after the bikini bathing two piece swim ware?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213442AAUd6yD</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213442AAUd6yD</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:34:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Weird high pitch chirp coming from hamster?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213501AA8cN8V</link><description>Just a few minutes ago I walked into my room, and i heard this chirp noise and I immediately checked my hamster and it sounded like it was her, so i woke her up and she stopped, maybe it was bedding in her nose? She was under some bedding, i'm not quite sure what it was and i googled it and cant find a good answer to it,</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213501AA8cN8V</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:35:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Im living with my dad now from a court order and my mom still has my dog?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213938AA3thJt</link><description>It is legally hers or thats what she said bc i dont even know if a dog can legally be someones. my dad bought the dog tho can i do anything legally other than ask pretty please as shes said no to several times note this is important as she mistreats my dog. not anything so serious that the dog would be legally taken from her but she puts him either on a short leash in the cage or not able to leave one room all the time. the dog fears her as she will yell at barely anything and sometimes hit and throw the dog but no marks i can prove also she barely gives it exercise and hes an australian shepherd that needs tons and when she goes on vacation she will leave the dogs home for days in a room with no care. I know thats illegal but thats the only thing other than hitting  and i cant prove it almost all these answers are telling me that im a minor and cant own a dog. yes i know that. no where in my question did I state that I legally owned this dog nor asked if I can own the dog so stop telling me i know. I just said my mom has my dog in my question because other than legally its my dog ok. i got my dog back</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706213938AA3thJt</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:39:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What jobs is hiring in Philadelphia, Pa for night shifts?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706214623AApoHbO</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706214623AApoHbO</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:46:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When you been given out in cricket do you watch the bowler and fielding team celebration?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706214818AAMooqb</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706214818AAMooqb</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:48:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: The commissioner of my league has past away. Can you change the setting so I can become the commissioner. My league was auto renewed.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215011AAJMNqC</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215011AAJMNqC</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:50:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who is more expensive in water repairs, a licensed plumber or the City Water Department, Houston TX?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215219AAP4Met</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706215219AAP4Met</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 22:52:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: DOES HORSE RADISH HAVE ANY BENEFITS FOR TOUR HEALTH?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163512AAZPRqL</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163512AAZPRqL</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:35:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Air Asia X, D7 flight, does anyone knows where is the call button for attendant located?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163448AA86ZAA</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163448AA86ZAA</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:34:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can you use a hammer drill for driving screws?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153814AAJ2tMY</link><description>I want a hammer drill because the walls of  our house is concrete and I want to place small cabinets. Do hammer drills drive screws as well?

If not, so I should buy a hammer drill and an impact drill as well? Or is there a two in 1 power tool that does that? WHAT brands do you recommend? Be specific please.. THNX!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153814AAJ2tMY</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 16:38:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a plant in soil in a pot. Its doing so well so quickly the roots have begun to grow out of the pot. What would you suggest?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706162519AASk1be</link><description>I put the pot soil &amp; all into a container of water until I can get to the store to get a new pot, soil, vitamins... I dont drive.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706162519AASk1be</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:25:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Best CHEAP place to fully furnish an apartment in the DFW area?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153702AAdArdh</link><description>Moving from CA to Fort Worth.....anyone local to that area that can tell me the best way to basically buy everything new?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153702AAdArdh</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 16:37:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What kind of paint can I use to make the back of my iPhone black?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706162143AAVtFgT</link><description>It's silver now.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706162143AAVtFgT</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:21:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Saudi Israeli?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163548AAFgtkr</link><description>is Saudi-Israeli relations be formal and direct? what are the results?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163548AAFgtkr</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:35:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to stop my towels from ripping into shreds?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163859AAvFnfF</link><description>Hello!
My towels keep getting holes in them and ripping into shreds in less than half a year. I have very hard water where i live, since i get my water from a free flowing well. Usually i wash my towels with cheap laundry detergent and no fabric softener and dry them without dryer sheets for and hour. I've tried all kinds of towels from really thick, heavy duty, expensive kinds to  cheap thin towels to no avail. Any ideas?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706163859AAvFnfF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:38:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What does everyone think of traveling alone for short vacations if none of your friends or family can go?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706164001AAbomx2</link><description>I previously had asked for locations on where to travel but figured out some locations I can go to. So now my main question is would anyone here travel alone if nobody else can go with them. I go to sporting events lunch movies alone from time to time when nobody else can go</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706164001AAbomx2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:40:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it okay to buy a hammer drill online?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706164639AAVzTqI</link><description>Many brands that I want are not available here in the hardware stores in the Philippines but when I search online, there are local online stores that sell famous brands. 

The disadvantages here is, first, I won't know if they are indeed brand new until I buy them. Another thing is I don't get to try it. Lastly,some have warranty, some have don't. The warranty isn't really useless since you have to ship that again and it is pretty expensive since these products are heavy. *I mean, the warranty IS useless...</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706164639AAVzTqI</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:46:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help on concelaing musket in home? BEST ANSWERS?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706165226AAXaBja</link><description>I need to hide a 51 inch Kentucky rifle in my bedroom but don't know where . If someone breaks in this is the last thing I need them to find .</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706165226AAXaBja</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:52:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I pack aresol hair spray in my checked luggage?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706165821AAObBW4</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706165821AAObBW4</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 17:58:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are most of the toilets in Malaysia and Thailand squat toilets?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170213AAFyU3T</link><description>Are Western Toilets easy to find there? Most hotels/restaurants?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170213AAFyU3T</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:02:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are most of the toilets in Malaysia and Thailand squat toilets?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170230AA1j2c5</link><description>Are Western Toilets easy to find there? Most hotels/restaurants? Stores?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170230AA1j2c5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why r blk ants all over my pine tree..they r literally falling out of when u walk by?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170501AA7VWTg</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170501AA7VWTg</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:05:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Unaccompanied Minor?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170944AAbKe01</link><description>I am gong to be buying a ticket for my 8 yr old niece to fly from Kansas City to San Antonio (2 hr). It says I will have to pay a $50 fee for unaccompanied minor service. It then says the flight attendant will check on her when duties allow, so what the hell am I paying for? She will sit in one spot for 2 hrs on a nonstop flight, her mom will sit with her until she gets on the flight and I will pick her up right when she gets off the flight. They won't be doing anything, she can read so finding her seat will be easy for her. Is there any way to get around this? I could understand if she had to change plans or have a layover, but come on, she will literally be in one spot the whole time.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706170944AAbKe01</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:09:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should i put aloe vera on water for it to grow roots?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706171731AAcZJuk</link><description>My dad brought a aloe vera pup or whatever, i cannot post a pocture of it, however it seemed to be cut, it has 6 leaves, it is small like 5 cm and he brought it in a cup with water for it to grow roots, but i am worried it does not work that way, how should i grow this plant? Or do i let it grow roots in the water?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706171731AAcZJuk</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:17:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hi i'm 13 and i mastbath more than i should. I'm worried because i haven't had my period in almost 2 months and i'm scared. Help please!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706171933AA2JWjy</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706171933AA2JWjy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:19:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is my package coming today?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706172123AAgA18o</link><description>I ordered something online and the USPS is shipping it. They gave me a code to track it and it says it should be here today(the mail hasn't come yet) but the last location was in MO. I live in MA.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706172123AAgA18o</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:21:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How difficult is it to leave America behind and move to Guam?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706172401AASKsoQ</link><description>I'm so tired of the rat race and cultural conflict in the US. Guam is a remote island, but since it's an American territory, I don't have to worry about immigration headaches, I just have to move and find a way to live and work there. Is it difficult for a US mainlander to start a new life in Guam?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706172401AASKsoQ</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:24:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to blow the dust out inside the wall when drilling a concrete wall?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706173431AAUpI0c</link><description>I have no problems with the dust falling... but it's kinda hard to get the dust out when drilling a concrete wall.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706173431AAUpI0c</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:34:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does shower steam contain germs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706173542AAsY9eF</link><description>Someone said showering in steam is like laying down with a clean body in filth and that everything comes right back on you</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706173542AAsY9eF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:35:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it safe for someone to sleep in the street in SF?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706174101AAUqF1P</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706174101AAUqF1P</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:41:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can i bring an acoustic guitar as a carry on?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706174445AAZtwZO</link><description>I fly out on Sun Country airlines and I would like to bring my guitar. I dont have a case which is probably not a good start to traveling with a guitar ,but I dont have time to go get one. Can I bring it as a carry on or is there a safe way to bring it?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706174445AAZtwZO</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:44:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do I need to apply a sealer first?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706175817AAVO1rM</link><description>I am getting ready to lay down engineered wood flooring.  2 rooms had carpet in them.  I need to pour some self leveling concrete on the rooms that had the carpet.  Do I need to put down primer first before pouring the concrete down before applying the concrete adhesive?  I am gluing the wood flooring down on first floor concrete slab.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706175817AAVO1rM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 18:58:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I rent student apartments in Germany?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706180011AATxesu</link><description>Hello! I'm planning to take a gap year in Germany with a Working Holiday Visa so I'm looking into housings. The student housings there look amazing. Does anyone know if I can also rent one without being a student or know one that would allow it? I might take up a language course there, would that make me eligible? Twenty First Student Living, the Fizz, etc etc.
Thank you!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706180011AATxesu</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:00:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: The power cord wasn't hooked to wall... cannot get anything even after replugging everything..?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706180850AATbdJT</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706180850AATbdJT</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:08:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My sister (pregnant, has a sensitive nose) smells a burning rubber smell coming from our vent or wall. The vent is inactive. What can it be?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181538AAMnKez</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181538AAMnKez</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:15:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the difference between a lag shield and a sleeve anchor?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181714AAJwdx5</link><description>I am using it on a concrete wall.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181714AAJwdx5</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:17:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the difference between a lag shield and a sleeve anchor?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181738AAiuyFF</link><description>I am using it on a concrete wall.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181738AAiuyFF</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:17:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How is Salem, Oregon? Thinking of moving to Salem, Oregon from Los Angeles. Please share your experience. Schools, employement, housing ect?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181949AALXyjd</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706181949AALXyjd</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:19:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help me settle this 'Vacation' debate please!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183145AAnQg5A</link><description>I am soon going to Canada for three months for an internship, I would consider this 'moving' to Canada, however my partner sees this a just a 'vacation'. Any opinions on what this really is? Thanks</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183145AAnQg5A</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:31:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should japan just ADMIT IT?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183716AARbz5E</link><description>everyone knows they did it</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183716AARbz5E</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:37:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Would you live in Jersey City or New York City?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183801AA2Wz7L</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706183801AA2Wz7L</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:38:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is God a Korean woman from South Korea?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184422AAb1jtq</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184422AAb1jtq</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:44:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Phoenix, Arizona or Austin, Texas?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184451AAcvFGL</link><description>I am 20 have lived in Phoenix Arizona all of my life and am considering moving to Austin Tx. I have visited about 4 times and am absolutely in love with it. My partner is there, and I am at a point in my life where I'm not stuck with a career or school. I have opportunity to start anything again, and I'm not sure what I want to do with my life. I have experienced the humidity in the summer and have to say that it is a lot better than dry heat personally. Should I move there? Need opinions</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184451AAcvFGL</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:44:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Which state should I move to out of these 3?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184528AA0BkvM</link><description>I'm graduating college next spring and I'm planning on moving to a different state. Right now I'm considering California, Texas, or Florida. In your experience, which of the 3 would you say is the best? Thanks!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184528AA0BkvM</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:45:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What s the best company or tour to go to Scotland?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184644AARby5n</link><description>I want to take my mom to Scotland next year, there s a lot of different options and it s all getting confusing. Has anyone been before or know if a good website for researching the best one for us. I want it to be about a week and not to physically demanding for her.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184644AARby5n</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:46:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does a septic manhole cover need a lock and chain?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184845AAdkjmv</link><description>I have a large heavy cement septic manhole cover.  The sewer inspector says this needs a chain and lock.  Is that true?  And if so, what is the cheapest way to install this?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706184845AAdkjmv</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:48:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I use AV gas with a Coleman 424-700 camp stove?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706185753AAtzT5l</link><description>Hi,

I just purchased a used Coleman 424-700 dual fuel camp stove, it says I can use regular gas or coleman fuel.
I was wondering if using AV gas would be better gas to use? Would it burn hotter ie. Could I get more heat from it?
I am curious because the STHIL weedeater I got the guy recommended AV gas because it s cleaner.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706185753AAtzT5l</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 19:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will anthurium bloom again?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706190725AAzsaMN</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706190725AAzsaMN</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:07:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Gardening Experts: Is it okay to plant peonies here?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706192643AAYv54y</link><description>My house faces east.  The south side of my house has a door into a large breezeway, maybe 15 feet wide.  To the south of the breezeway is a two-car attached garage with two separate single garage doors, not one big one, so it's a big garage.  I want to plant peonies along the outside of the south wall of my garage, which gets plenty of sun.

I know peonies attract ants.  Ants are how they pollinate.  But because of they attract ans, people have said I shouldn't plant them along my house.

My question is is that really too close to my house.  I mean, it's right up against my house, but it's the attached garage on the other side of an attached breezeway, both of which are outside rooms.  It's a good 40 to 50 feet from the actual inside of my house.  

Is that too close?  Would I be inviting ants?  Also, my house is limestone.  Would there be an issue of the rocks heating up too much from the direct sun for the peonies? I don't think so because peonies seem to thrive in direct sun and heat, but I just wanted to check. Oh, and when should peonies be planted?  Is it a spring planting or a fall planting or can I do it now?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706192643AAYv54y</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:26:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I use a 17 inch laptop on airplane tray?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193016AAo6p9u</link><description>I have a gaming 17 inch laptop and I was wondering if I can use it while travelling on a plane using seat tray. I will be on A380 plane and I have never traveled on that plane.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193016AAo6p9u</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:30:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a little giant model pmo-650. How do you reset the reset button. My pump does t even try to run.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193125AA6yw3p</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193125AA6yw3p</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:31:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I fix up my wood balcony on the second floor on a budget?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193215AAfH8Wu</link><description>Recently my grandma has been sick so we moved her down stairs and I moved up stairs. Now this house is old and has a lot of problems. The room I moved into has a sliding glass door that opens up to a balcony and steps on the side. I have 3 dogs and 3 cats. They all love using the balcony to go in and out. My problem with that is that the wood is rotting and is weak. I'm afraid to walk out on it. My pit bull is 83 pounds and my rottypit mix pup is supposed to get up to 100 pounds. I'm only 125 so if it's weak for me it will be weak for my pups. I'm also moving out in a year and dont want to put to mucn money into something thats not going to stay with. Is there any way to make it safe to walk on. Let the dogs sun bath out on it have a nice little sitting spot with plants and humming bird feeders. Would putting a big plank of wood over the old rotting wood work. Have the wait spread out instead of all on one spot or should I just close the door and lock it up. Dont want my dogs falling throwing and getting hurt badly but I would love to use it</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193215AAfH8Wu</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:32:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help with Disney Worlds Magic Bands?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193734AAAe9pf</link><description>My friends and I went to Disney World recently, and we had magic bands. We did not have any memory maker or anything like that. We were not told that we had to pay for the pictures, they only told us that it would be on our magic bands, so we would just have the photographer use the magic band of the person who was the closest. So now we have pictures on 3 different Magic band accounts and we don t want to pay $60 each for the pictures if there is a way that we could combine them and only pay $60 for the day.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706193734AAAe9pf</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:37:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I fix my wood balcony on a budget?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706195018AASCDYU</link><description>My grandma recently got sick so we moved her downstairs and I moved upstairs. Everything in this house is old and has problems. The room I moved into has glass sliding doors that lead out to a wood balcony with steps down the side. The problem with this balcony is that the wood is old rotting away and is very weak. I have 3 dogs and 3 cats. One of my dog's is a pitbull and he weighs 83 pounds my second dog is a Rottie pit mix and the vet estimates he'll be around 100 pounds. I weigh 125 and when I step out on it it feels like it's weak and going to fall throw. All my pets love to go in and out throw that door but my fear is my dogs even maybe one of my cats falling throw. I would love to make a little chill spot with hanging plants and hummingbird feeders and sit outside with my pets as they sun bath. I'm also moving out in a year. Is there anyway to fix is check and easy. I was thinking a big plank of wood and laying it over the old rotting wood. That way when me or the pets step on it the weight would be spread out instead of on one spot. Would that work? Is there a better way or should I just shut the door and lock it for good</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706195018AASCDYU</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:50:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will soviet union be reestablished as state?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706195419AAH4txN</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706195419AAH4txN</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 20:54:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should i prune my avocado plant?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706200728AAQjWz2</link><description>it's about 12 inches and i never pruned it once</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706200728AAQjWz2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:07:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it safe to go to Chicago, New York, Washington D.C, Saint Louis, Atlanta, New Orleans, San Diego, Los Angeles, or Seattle alone?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706200959AApoASo</link><description>I'm wanting to go on a vacation and I have to go by myself since I have no family, friends, or partner to go with. I was curious how safe these cities are and if I would be safe being in these cities alone. I'm interested in these cities to go to there museums, Aquariums, or Zoos. I'm also interested in going near these cities mountains or scenery of water(ocean, Lake, or River) if there is one in all of these cities.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706200959AApoASo</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:09:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Last year in I got bullied ALOT!! They called me some nasty things and flipped me off too many times any advice for next year?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201340AAW7Jpl</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201340AAW7Jpl</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:13:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What do you all think about this burberry bag for a male?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201838AA78Jiy</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706201838AA78Jiy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 21:18:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What material is this blanket?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225205AAJElGS</link><description>I'm trying to decide how to wash it, and it doesn't have a label. Does it look like wool?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225205AAJElGS</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:52:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When writing a story, how do you stay in past tense or present tense, and do you have to have a reason for which you use?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225603AAnKKif</link><description>So I write a lot of fiction in past tense.  Like, "John felt that neither of should have ever felt that way.  We needed to bond more." So I use -ed at the end of need, and use felt instead of feels.  

To stay in the tense do you just have to listen to how it sounds?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225603AAnKKif</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Packing question?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225617AA4yvJ2</link><description>So I'm going on a mini vacation from Saturday to Tuesday how many outfits would I need?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706225617AA4yvJ2</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 23:56:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is there a white sandy beach near Cross City, Florida ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230212AATZWgC</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230212AATZWgC</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:02:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I just bought a hamster and its been non-stop running on the wheel even though its 3 in the afternoon, what s going on? Is this normal?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230518AAqphm1</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230518AAqphm1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help with hair removal on my neck and chest?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230735AAE7kZH</link><description>A couple of years back, I began shaving my neck because a friend of mine said I had long dark hairs, and I was embarrassed. I also began shaving my chest not long after. I regretted it immediately, but it was too late to turn back. 

My issue is that my neck always has either red or black bumps after shaving, and it looks really bad. To avoid this on my chest, I started plucking the dark hairs, only for there to be red, pimple-like bumps all over it. I ve tried everything from using warm rags to soften the hairs to exfoliating to moisturizing after, but my skin never looks normal.

Please help me to remedy this. As a female, it s so embarrassing. I can t wear my hair up without makeup on my neck, and I m too embarrassed to wear v-neck shirts. :(</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230735AAE7kZH</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:07:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why did the Liberal Party of Australia call themselves liberal?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230904AA7dziU</link><description>I have done a little bit of reading about the party and they formed in 1945 to apparently combat the spread of socialism and communism. It's strange that Australia went that route because after WW2 the UK became more socialist. The first elected government after the Second World War introduced the NHS (National Health Service) largely as a way to make sure everyone who fought in the war and the families who were affected had free access to the health care that they required. Australia didn't really do a lot of fighting in the war and were relatively unharmed so the need for free health care probably wasn't as pressing for them.

Despite claiming to be economically liberal, the Liberal Party has introduced more protectionist policies and interventionism than any other government in Australia and are fervently conservative in social aspects. It was the ALP that started TPP negotiations that would have potentially liberated trade between some of the largest world markets.

Despite the Liberal's best efforts to restrict socialism, socialist healthcare was introduced in Australia in 1975. It was called Medibank initially but is now known as Medicare, and has near universal approval. This  not only helped Australians at home but also abroad because it lead to Reciprocal Health Care Agreements with the United Kingdom and ten other countries entitling Australian residents to reciprocal free health care rights while in one of these countries.

In short, the Liberals are not liberal.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230904AA7dziU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:09:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Dog peeing for several minutes to an hour?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230942AAdtjTe</link><description>the other day, my friends dog (around 11 years old believe) started peeing inside so they let him in and i guess he wad either on and off peeing or straight peeing for several minutes. they let him back inside about 40 minutes later and he was still peeing ? he hasnt done thus since. the reason im asking is because my friends parents are tight w money, getting asked to leave their place and movin to another. i cannot myself afford to take him to the vet either. has anybody have a clue on what this could be ?? and anyway we can help at home ?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706230942AAdtjTe</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:09:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do they have ATM in Iquitos,Peru?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231118AAdDkvh</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231118AAdDkvh</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:11:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are Beefsteak tomatoes determinant and if so what will happen if I pruned it?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231317AAj7ILA</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231317AAj7ILA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:13:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why does my kitten scratch at my bedroom door at night when I'm trying to sleep?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231718AAgIe50</link><description>He also whines and cries too. 
Why won't he go sleep somewhere else? 
What should I do</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706231718AAgIe50</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:17:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Pro wrestling: who's winning this year's G1 climax?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706232536AA3Xfr4</link><description>If you don't know who I'm talking about please don't answer, but if you do who's your pick? For me it's Tetsuya Naito, he's the only one of the big four who's not holding a championship or in a current feud. Kenny Omega is first and current IWGP United States heavyweight champion, Tanahashi is the current IC champ and Okada is in his 5th heavyweight reign. Naito is currently in limbo and I'd be down for a wrestle kingdom 12 mainevent match between Okada and Naito. So who do you think is gonna win?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706232536AA3Xfr4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:25:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: HELP! Hair salon question. How can I fix this?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706232941AAXXkOQ</link><description>So I work for a hair salon and a client booked a 2 hour appointment. Well the issue is 1. I didn t hear their name or number 2. The time I gave them on Sunday doesn t work as he will have a client at that time. So I am unable to figure out who or what to call to try and reschedule, and they called on our land phone so I don t know how to trace back all of the calls. What do I do? I don t want him mad but I know I should tell him.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706232941AAXXkOQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:29:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Has anyone ever had bad feelings about a flight, then went on the flight and everything went fine? I'm having doubts about my flight safety.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233106AA9b7t9</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233106AA9b7t9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:31:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I make my legs look amazing in a dress?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233506AAqZqNH</link><description>Wearing a short dress at the weekend, I don't normally leg my legs out...as they're very pale, I've old stretch marks on the backs of my legs, and knobbly knees...but I've been building confidence so gonna brave it. 

I can't wear tights, also I can't get the Sally Hansen Airbrush Legs (I'm on a tight budget). 

I use laser hair removal, plus I exfoliate and use moisturizer daily, so my legs are smooth. 
I'm thinking of adding foundation to my moisturizer, also using a little coconut oil for glow. 

Any other tips?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233506AAqZqNH</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:35:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do you create your characters?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233631AAudsVq</link><description>When you already have a basic idea of who your character is, what do you do then? What's the process? Do you have a file in which you write everything about the character? Do you do questionnares? Do you simply write the characters from your head without any previous preparations??</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233631AAudsVq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:36:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What's a good tribute to the owner of a dog who just died?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233743AA7LmSz</link><description>The dog just died and I wish to write a card to the owner.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233743AA7LmSz</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:37:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do Some People think we Sicilians have Black ancestry When its is Actually Arab ancestry?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233839AA1CIky</link><description>I am not trying to be a racist butt We dont have black ancestry We have Arab ancestry Greek Ancestry Norman Spanish thats why we look darker than other europeans</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706233839AA1CIky</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do i stop my cat from jumping and attacking me and others?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234110AAJ3pUw</link><description>my 1 year old male cat who isn't neutered is a nice cat and he'll be sweet but sometimes he'll have his moments when i don't let him out of my room or move him lightly with my feet and then he'll jump and attack my leg. he'll start biting and scratching very harshly and then when i get him off of my leg he'll aim for my arm and jump to my face. i can't let him out of my room because he'll fight with my other cats. i'm going to start letting him out of my room once we get him neutered this week. but will neutering make a difference? i just want him to stop attacking. he attacks sometimes but i want him to stop completely so what do i do</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234110AAJ3pUw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:41:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Am I considered ambidextrous?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234413AADNLdr</link><description>I write and eat with my left hand, while my right hand is used for almost everything else. The only time I can use both are whenever I use knives or scissors or drawing (yes, I can draw with both hands, but I can only write with my left.).</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234413AADNLdr</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:44:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Im trying to replace the trrs jack on my gaming headset w/ mic. Only problem is that the wires colors are odd.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234432AAhPh8F</link><description>I have seen a lot about a red, blue, green and copper. Mine has an extra wire that seems to be red and copper in a spiral. What is this and where does it go?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234432AAhPh8F</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:44:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why did Justin Trudeau bow to the Queen? Is she the boss of him and is he more lowly than her?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234637AAIzP5A</link><description>I thought he was a democratically elected world leader. Why would he be more lowly and under the supervision of an unelected person who lives in the United Kingdom? The bowing he did is seen in link, in the third video from the top of story. 

http://m.huffpost.com/us/entry/us_595dd939e4b02e9bdb0a3887</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234637AAIzP5A</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:46:37 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hey, can anyone help me find the title of this book?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234743AAQqXvB</link><description>I don t remember a whole lot, but there s a few key things I do remember, he s caught making out with a girl in the beginning by I think his uncle, I m not sure, but I remember that because they used the word "Macking" multiple times. Then, the main plot, his house and parents vanish and he finds out that they were never his parents in the first place. Then his uncle tells him everything and his uncle takes him to like a different universe or something along those lines. Again, not even sure if it s his uncle. That s about it. I know it s not a lot to go on, but I remember it being a really good book and I would really like to find it.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706234743AAQqXvB</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:47:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: On a scale 1 to 10, how would you rate Juventud Guerrera, in his prime?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235016AAiXq94</link><description>Speed-
Aerial-
Agility-
Stamina-
Conditioning-
Intensity-
Strength-
Technical-
Match Quality-
Striking-
Rudo/Heel
Technico/Face
Attire-
Charisma-</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235016AAiXq94</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:50:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What steps must a person take when going for a swim in a YMCA swimming pool when they have one-eye?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235051AAsrsxb</link><description>What about if they go swimming in an ocean?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235051AAsrsxb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:50:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where can I take my shoes to get them professionally restored and cleaned?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235153AAkqkay</link><description>I m willing to ship, but the place has to reputable.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235153AAkqkay</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:51:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I've had two of my piercings (tragus + nose) get bumps even though i clean them everyday with the piercing wash they gave me. Any tips?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235356AAb37NK</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706235356AAb37NK</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 00:53:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What makes poetry special, if it is special? That is, how is it different from other forms of language such as everyday speech, fiction, etc?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707000229AAwcCp8</link><description>What makes poetry special, if it is special? That is, how is it different from other forms of language such as everyday speech, fiction, nonfiction in print, the dialogue in a play, or the wording used in advertisements? Is the language in one genre of poetry more like that of another genre or more like language that you find outside of poetry?

Think about one or more ways people use language, and compare it to the language you find in poetry. Discuss why language seems to take different forms, or why it makes sense to categorize it by form, situation, medium, purpose, and audience, for example.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707000229AAwcCp8</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:02:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it a stereotype if someone thinks I am from New York City because my first name is Tony?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707000230AAu2Nat</link><description>I have had this happen to me only once in my life. Is it a stereotype of people with this first name?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707000230AAu2Nat</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:02:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why is my guinea pig biting my other guinea pigs butt?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001012AAkt1G0</link><description>I have three guinea pigs, two younger males and a larger female. The female keeps following my longer haired male around and nipping his butt. She only does it to the specific one and not the other male.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001012AAkt1G0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:10:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can i clean a stained jordan retro 13 backpack (white)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001152AAjlqdd</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001152AAjlqdd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:11:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Any chance the Mississippi Rebels will win the national championship?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001157AA3NgB2</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001157AA3NgB2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:11:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is a true scary story you have?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001222AAPkQqK</link><description>Any scary story you can think of.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001222AAPkQqK</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:12:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is urbanistica?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001255AAaqm24</link><description>A. town planning
B. urban aesthetics 
C. sociological value of public and private space 
D. All the above
E. 2 &amp; 3 only</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001255AAaqm24</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:12:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: BAGGAGE ALLOWANCE FROM DAVAO TOPORTLAND ON DELTA?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001319AAB9EOS</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001319AAB9EOS</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:13:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What does "anata wa aho des" and "mo watashi sokoni iranaio" means in english?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001433AADOEmG</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707001433AADOEmG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:14:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: By the middle of the thirteen century mercenary armies were no longer used by the communes. True or false?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002109AAfLa5B</link><description>For an ancient Italy history course. *I meant medieval history.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002109AAfLa5B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:21:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Which type of watch could I get, analog or digital?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002230AAGenOG</link><description>Since I have a digital watch that is two years old along with a broken wriststrap.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002230AAGenOG</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:22:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What was not permitted to take place in the Palazzo Pubblico in Sienna?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002246AA4CJKt</link><description>A. Children couldn't eat figs
B. No bloodsports could occur
C. Women could not spin yarn
D. All the above
E. 2 &amp; 3 only
My guess was B. Any help is appreciated.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002246AA4CJKt</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Strange medical episode while swimming... What happened?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002318AAD8Whp</link><description>This happened to me some time ago (like a decade). I was swimming with friends and family in an indoor swimming pool. I had just jumped in and been submerged for a few seconds. I had only gone down a foot or two. Nothing unusual about the descent or ascent until I emerged to breathe and couldn't. I may as well have been trying to breathe water, the air felt so dense and my lungs felt so small. Through much gasping and sputtering (which caught no one's attention amazingly) I managed to grasp the pool ledge and get my breathing back to normal.
I always thought it might've been the Benz and when I ask the people who were there they don't remember what I'm referring to.
Could it have been from landing in the water at a weird angle?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002318AAD8Whp</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:23:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the name of the Chinese martial arts clothing? Ip Man most noticeably wears the uniform.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002636AA5N5Fr</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707002636AA5N5Fr</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:26:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who's right about the dog situation??????</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003225AAQVpad</link><description>My dog is VERY overweight and I'm trying to make him lose weight. Sometimes I take him on 3 mile walks but if I don't do 3, he's always doing at least one mile. 

I feed him twice a day morning and night and kinda eyeball it and not fill up the whole bowl. 

He's still hungry when I feed him but I don't feed him anymore until the next feeding which is at night. 


My dad thinks I should feed him more since he's licking his bowl looking for more food and acting hungry, but I think I shouldn't feed him more because I'm trying to get him to lose weight and giving him more food will defeat the purpose.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003225AAQVpad</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:32:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Giovanni Villani dedicated two chapters to this aspect of Florentine urban architecture?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003729AAO6Iaw</link><description>A. Fountains
B. Palaces
C. Walls
D. Towers</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003729AAO6Iaw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:37:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My room stinks?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003939AAObNhk</link><description>Moved to that room a week ago. There were 2 bags of unwashed clothes. I cleaned the room got ride of everything that may cause the odor still the room smells bad.
Any ideas on how to get rid of that smell</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707003939AAObNhk</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:39:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone explain this creepypasta to me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004125AAwQ8uP</link><description>http://creepypasta.wikia.com/wiki/Union_Parish_Diary Copy the link down, read the pasta, then come back and answer my question.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004125AAwQ8uP</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:41:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it plagiarism to use a movie joke in a fictional book i'm writing?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004317AAOivY9</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004317AAOivY9</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:43:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should I get an exterminator?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004428AAVUJYS</link><description>I have found a couple bed bugs in multiple bedrooms in my house, but i have looked around with a flashlight in all possible places they could be and see none. so i dont think I have an infestation. should I still call an exterminator or should I just use a special bed bug spray</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004428AAVUJYS</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:44:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Grease Musical Audition tips?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004436AAjRWG4</link><description>I'm auditioning for Grease the musical. The song I'm singing is "You don't own me" by Lesley Gore because I'm interested in the part of "Rizzo." My auditio is in 4 days. Any tips to stand out?
There will be a vocal audition and a dance audition after.
What should I wear? Something I can dance in obviously, but actual dance clothes or casual clothes? How should I do my makeup?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004436AAjRWG4</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:44:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to look older without makeup?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004439AAtB4UJ</link><description>I'm going into high school next year, however I look like a 12 year old.  This wouldn't be much of a problem but most other people look 16/17 years old.  I don't want to look like I'm trying too hard or wear too much makeup, but I have a baby face.  I know I shouldn't care what people think but it'd give me way more confidence to look at least a year or two older.  Also I'm kinda short for my age (5' 4") so that doesn't help my case, and I recently cut my hair to my collar. One which makes me look even younger than usual.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004439AAtB4UJ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:44:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do you ever eat at airport restaurants after flying into your home airport?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012047AAN9WiR</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012047AAN9WiR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:20:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it becoming obvious cubs have lost mojo?bye bye,2017?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012201AA7LGMg</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012201AA7LGMg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:22:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to do great at a musical theatre audition?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012240AAoOtoE</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707012240AAoOtoE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:22:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is your opinion and prediction for Conor McGregor vs Floyd Mayweather Jr?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013401AAomMhW</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013401AAomMhW</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:34:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I get rid of odd smell in apartment?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013546AAgenrm</link><description>Our apartment was recently renovated in a historic building. All hard wood floors...no carpet, wallpaper, or air vents (there's a single room unit AC) When we first moved in, the place smelled fine...but now it's got some odd sour odor. I can't really explain what it smells like. It's not necessarily bad, but it's not pleasant. We're generally clean people, and when I deep clean the entire apartment, the odor is less, but still distinguishable. I'll open all the windows and air out the rooms almost every day...no help!  I CANNOT figure out what's causing it! It seems worst in the bedroom. Any ideas what it could be, or how to cover it up (without using candles, Fabreez, or any chemicals like that)?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013546AAgenrm</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:35:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: So Me and my grandpa might be going somewhere but i have to figure out where were gonna go and i was wondering where you think we should go?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013746AAJMWjH</link><description>So me and my grandparents and my two sisters and my cousin were gonna go to new york and then my grandpa me and my cousin were gonna go to niagra falls but my cousins mom wont let him go because its her week so were not gonna go except for the girls but we might be able to go without my cousin if i find a good/cool place to go but idk where we could go... it would be after we went to ny with the girls and then we would go somewhere else, just me and my grandpa... where do you think we should go? im 13 and hes 60</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707013746AAJMWjH</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:37:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What are the benefits of Running/Training with a Training Mask?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014057AAlaH0P</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014057AAlaH0P</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:40:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I m a defender in soccer and I am at this camp and I played very **** against these good players I d like to know some tips to help me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014058AAhZF7H</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014058AAhZF7H</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:40:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How does cultural diffusion play into the migration and the impact on North American?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014246AAmdQSY</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014246AAmdQSY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:42:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is a coping sander and is that the same thing as a coping saw?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014330AAwvUlU</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014330AAwvUlU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:43:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Job estimate?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014443AA0Nckd</link><description>hi, everyone

this is Tim. I just start my business in residential remodeling. my first client would like to do the following stuff:

bathroom remodel: 5ft*11ft bathroom

take out the bathtub. put concrete on the ground to build a shower. replace faucet inside the shower and build a "chair" inside. add a two level shower soap dish "inside" the wall. 

replace a new toilet, install a new outlet next to the toilet, replace vanity, install a new light and a fan on top of the shower.

tile the entire bathroom, including wall, floor, total 270ft.

how much should I charge for this project? only labor, customer buy material. I am in atlanta btw.

looking forward to hear from any professional contractor. thanks so much~!!!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014443AA0Nckd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:44:43 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is Russ Smith going to make the NBA?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014618AAkSJAg</link><description>He's putting up big numbers on a daily basis</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014618AAkSJAg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:46:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Attempting to start a business predicting point spreads for football. Advice anyone?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014720AAcLud0</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014720AAcLud0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:47:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I'm a boy who wants to wear makeup.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014741AAXcDE2</link><description>I'm a teenage boy who wants to start wearing makeup, (and yes I am gay before you ask). Could I have some advice on how to get started? What I should start doing first?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014741AAXcDE2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:47:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: In GFW, could LAX pass a drug test?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014928AA77q8J</link><description>They drink more than APA. I know some blunts go around that table too</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707014928AA77q8J</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:49:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What kind of power does a tattoo gun take?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015236AAevlaH</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015236AAevlaH</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:52:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Nose piercing wont go all the way through?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015338AAhpSh6</link><description>i have to take my nose piercing out for work every day and usually i have it out for 2 days straight with no problems. today i had it out for about 12 hours, tried to put it back in and it wont go through. ive tried for about 20 minutes and it started to bleed so i stopped. i cant see the hole under my nose but i do have a pimple in my nose, could that be why it wont go through? what should i do?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015338AAhpSh6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:53:38 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do frogs croak!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015549AAgI4uq</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015549AAgI4uq</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:55:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do frogs croak!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015603AAC3KRn</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015603AAC3KRn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:56:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do frogs croak!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015613AALmerT</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015613AALmerT</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:56:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is my pomeranian fur weird?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015620AA8K0uu</link><description>Look here, my pom got some very soft fur on the side of his body
But, the fur on his back is different
down his spine the fur is stif and rough
and the color is different
My pom is 6 month-ish
What do you guys think ?
is it the shampoo or something else ?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015620AA8K0uu</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I got the first Twinrix shot in August of last year. Missed the 2nd and 3rd. Do I have to start over or can I just get the 2nd now?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015916AAnEx7g</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015916AAnEx7g</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:59:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is a FID needed to posses black powder in MA ? BESTANSWERS?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015954AA7Mzz6</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707015954AA7Mzz6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:59:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to do this animation technique?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020021AANxFln</link><description>Hey! 

I was wondering what kind of software/technique I could use to create a smiler effect to the background animation of the stills. There is a video showing how the animation was made, however this part was not talked about. Any help would be much appreciated thanks xxx

https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aygFh5oToN4</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020021AANxFln</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:00:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My top fin filter pump broke and killed my beta need to purchase a new pump for a 2.5 gallon tank. Please advise. Thanks, deanna?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020024AAoUqSB</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020024AAoUqSB</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:00:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I reach you by phone. Need a small topfin filter pump. thanks, deanna?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020148AAPTGKN</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020148AAPTGKN</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do you remove a fabric dye stain from carpet?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020506AAB8kSL</link><description>Got dye stuck in the carpet. Tried to clean with laundry detergent and water, but this just spread the mess.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020506AAB8kSL</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:05:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Cat quit using litter box?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020701AAVfR6g</link><description>My 12 year old cat (whom I've had since he was 6 months) randomly quit using the litter box and poops on my bed.  I put him in the crate with a litter box for a day, but it didn't help.  What can I do?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020701AAVfR6g</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:07:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My friend is quitting gymnastics but I really don t want her to! What can I do to make her stay?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020916AAsxZ9U</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707020916AAsxZ9U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:09:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is coconut oil really worth using for your face?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707021633AAEw3qM</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707021633AAEw3qM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:16:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Whats a cool shotgun you think i should get?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707021922AAJYnBk</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707021922AAJYnBk</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:19:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who will win this match card at WWE Great Balls of Fire and why? What is your prediction for this sunday?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022308AAoBYIg</link><description>1. Neville vs. Akira Tozawa - WWE Cruiserweight Championship Match (Pre-Show)

2. Brock Lesnar vs. Samoa Joe	- WWE Universal Championship Match

3. Roman Reigns vs. Braun Strowman - Ambulance Match

4. Alexa Bliss vs. Sasha Banks - WWE Raw Women's Championship Match

5. Seth Rollins vs. Bray Wyatt

6. Enzo Amore vs. Big Cass

7. The Miz vs. Dean Ambrose - WWE Intercontinental Championship Match

8. Cesaro and Sheamus vs. The Hardy Boyz - 30-minute Iron Man match for the WWE Raw Tag Team Championship Match</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022308AAoBYIg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:23:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What type of weather symbolizes fear?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022539AAJaj7J</link><description>So, I'm writing a music piece called "Emotional Weather." I had the sun and moon symbolize happiness and the rain symbolize sadness. What type of weather would symbolize fear?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022539AAJaj7J</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:25:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: No other country takes hockey seriously the way Canada does?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022821AAemX4U</link><description>Agree?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022821AAemX4U</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:28:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Did ESPN fire Britt McHenry because she was super hot?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022916AAnxYA2</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022916AAnxYA2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:29:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do Western Hognoses make good pets for first-time snake owners?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022950AAtBP5w</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707022950AAtBP5w</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:29:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Anyone else find the poster Alice annoying?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023002AAyYZT5</link><description>I do.  She hates the New York Yankees more than she loves her own Boston Red Sox.  All she ever talks about on here is her hatred for the Yankees and it would kill her to say something positive about them.  She also has an anime girl with an Red Sox hat on set as her avatar.  She gives real Red Sox fans a bad name.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023002AAyYZT5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:30:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Cat owners: how do I make my cat feel less depressed?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023449AAlH1Xd</link><description>After taking my cat to the vet he unfortunately has to wear a cone for 2 weeks. The minute we got home his personality changed a lot: he became more scared and shaky, has been eating less, goes to the bathroom less and just stays in bed all day now. I know he hates the cone and I feel guilty making him wear it but it s for his own good and health. Is there anything I can do to make my cat feel comfortable again without having to remove the cone?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023449AAlH1Xd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:34:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How did you prepare for your first puppy?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023907AA6yxVb</link><description>Just asking :)</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707023907AA6yxVb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:39:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Umpire question?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707024021AA3caTc</link><description>Bases loaded, 2 out. Grounder hit to 2nd baseman. Runner on first forgets to run and is tagged out, but before he is tagged, the run scores. Does the run count?
*I am a 15 y/o umpire and in a 10u game this happened. I said the run counted, but all 4 coaches except 1 disagreed with me and were yelling at me. Was I correct?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707024021AA3caTc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:40:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What are the benefits of ladybugs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707024400AA2XAxo</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707024400AA2XAxo</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:44:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do budgies click their beaks?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025228AA7BGnz</link><description>I got a new budgie recently, and as I was sitting with it, I noticed it started to click its beak. After a while, it stopped and was now opening and closing its beak silently as if it was speaking. What does this mean? Is it just scared?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025228AA7BGnz</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:52:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are you commiting the Tu quoque logical fallacy when?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025326AAUkgiI</link><description>you accuse the person of hypocrisy without receiving any criticism first?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025326AAUkgiI</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Does anyone have 25 off 50 haute cash for July 2017?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025450AAbXevR</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025450AAbXevR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:54:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it bad to keep smelling this?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025515AAasECc</link><description>I have some vinyl tubing in my room and it has an odor it's quite strong I could smell it from a few feet away is it bad to keep inhaling? I'm expecting to sleep close to it should I move it out of my room or?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025515AAasECc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:55:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What would be the hair color of a baby?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025519AAyZIPd</link><description>If the mother has red hair (like German red hair) and the father has dark brown hair what would their baby's hair color be? Also if the mother has wavy hair and the dad has curly hair what would the hair texture be? Can you please also answer the question about hair texture?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025519AAyZIPd</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:55:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the hard black thing on my dog?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025534AAL6qko</link><description>It comes and goes away. It will eventually fall off.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025534AAL6qko</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:55:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How did Martin Luther King change American Law?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025540AAKCxm7</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025540AAKCxm7</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:55:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Teenagers backpacking across Europe?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025620AAwOkHN</link><description>My boyfriend and i are going to be backpacking along europe for about a month and we will be staying w family and friends for the most parts so we wont be paying for hostels and we plan on eating bread and coffee for most of the trip (no eating out, basically living off of the bare minimum amount of food) and for the first two or three weeks we will be staying with my boyfriends family so we wont have to pay for food or shelter or anything (except drinks when we go out or other small things) With the plane tickets and eurail passes aside how much should we bring with us for spending money realistically. Right now were thinking about $500 each but that doesnt seem like enough to me, but then again we arent staying in hostels or hotels and we wont be eating out at all. Also if you have any tips on backpacking we would appreciate it :)</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025620AAwOkHN</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Got a tattoo and I think its smudged!!! Help!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025806AA8a8SN</link><description>i got a tattoo a few days ago and i think its fading from over moisturizing but that s not the point. I think the ink smudged somehow and left some dots where my tattoo isn t (sorry that isn t too descriptive) but Is that possible? Will it go away? Or can i cover it up? It hasn t fully healed yet.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025806AA8a8SN</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:58:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hello, I am having hair growth from my brow to my hairline, is this normal?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025926AAUnxGn</link><description>I suppose this hair has been growing for a bit, but since I am blonde I have not noticed it until presented with the correct light. I am just wondering if this is normal, and if it will grow to the same legenth as the rest of my hair eventually. Thank you your time</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707025926AAUnxGn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 03:59:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is Rudy Gay still a good basketball player?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030031AAlUWy0</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030031AAlUWy0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:00:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will the Warriors lose 15 regular season games next season?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030139AAVcA94</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030139AAVcA94</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:01:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why are the Spurs signing old players?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030204AA9WOsD</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030204AA9WOsD</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:02:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is this story true? Was Chuck Zito beaten up by a smaller and amateur mma fighter in Boston?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030223AAr7yNn</link><description>I've heard a story about chuck Zito going into a Irish bar in Boston and talking sh.t. He was confronted by a amateur mixed martial artist who was a shorter, tatted up and built Irish American  guy with a pretty face and dark blond hair. He said in a loud and harsh tone "yo chuck, let's take it outside" and from accounts I've heard, Zito got whooped into being humble. I'm told both got their hits in , but Zito was the obvious loser and down for the count. This supposedly happened not too long after the Jean Claude Van Dam incident that was in 98, I believe this was 2000-2001. How can someone who's such a tough guy and professional (not amateur) fighter get beat in a street fight by a smaller brawler</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030223AAr7yNn</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:02:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why has the studio not put WW3 into production yet after the major box office hits WW2 and WW1?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030420AAC9kHu</link><description>Is it due to the screenplay being stuck in development hell? Are they actors demanding too much money? Any other reason? Does anybody know?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030420AAC9kHu</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:04:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can you tell me the difference between me and Queen Latifah and Gabourey Sidibe?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030512AAFBYWv</link><description>Yes I'm ugly right? You human beings think I don't know what you did to my face that made me look like them right? You stole my beauty, youth, growth, and blessings. Then you changed my face to the two of them spiritually and physically. When I was first born into this world many years ago this is not how I looked. I was beautiful. I know that someone did something to my head and body. The person is a coward and a witch for stealing my youth and trying to turn me into an old lady even though I am only 25 years old. Now my body is filled with wrinkles. Human beings are evil.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030512AAFBYWv</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:05:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who was the president when you were born?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030601AAXnWsb</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030601AAXnWsb</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:06:01 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is there anyway I can receive my mail while abroad if I don't have a address to sent it to?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030702AAwt79X</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707030702AAwt79X</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:07:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Best dog pee poo remover carpet?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031006AAwDPoT</link><description>Can you actually have the smell fully disappear?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031006AAwDPoT</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:10:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should I get a turtle or a chameleon and why?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031126AAxtDnE</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031126AAxtDnE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:11:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should I quit basketball?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031242AA90dVM</link><description>I am going into my 8th grade year and have played since 5th grade. I'm a starter and play post. I really love my team and the coach but basketball isn't really in my heart anymore. The high school coaches always tell me they're looking forward to me playing for high school, but I don't really want to play. I also play volleyball and cheer, and cheer and basketball run into each other a lot. I am pretty good at volleyball, and my parents are always talking to me about getting a scholarship for basketball, but I want a scholarship for volleyball more than anything. I want to quit basketball and really focus on volleyball, but I don't want to make the coaches, the team, or my parents mad. My dad is constantly getting on me about practicing basketball outside of practice, but when it comes to volleyball, just tells me that what we do in practice is fine and doesn't push me to practice outside of school practice. I really love volleyball WAY more than basketball, but I feel like I'm playing for others, and not myself. I just don't love it anymore :/</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031242AA90dVM</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:12:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: People who make covers on Wattpad?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031305AAcyMt1</link><description>Does anyone know people who will make covers for you on Wattpad? The girl who usually helps me isn t online right now... let me know xoxo.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031305AAcyMt1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:13:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What's the difference in holister super skinny and jeggings? What ones are tighter?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031313AAusuxh</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031313AAusuxh</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:13:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Nylon/polyester vintage fabrics in drier safe?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031356AA6r2LE</link><description>nylon/polyester shorts, sport shorts
can it catch fire?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031356AA6r2LE</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:13:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone teach me the correct form to running &amp; weight lifting?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031359AAzoE32</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031359AAzoE32</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:13:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is there any fictional world's similar to the show Storm Hawks where people live on floating islands?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031520AA5tE5h</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031520AA5tE5h</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:15:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Como entro a mi correo olvide mi contra sena,anteriormente me hacian dos pregunts?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031541AAxHslO</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031541AAxHslO</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:15:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone help me with job interview attire?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031752AAZxB2h</link><description>I was laid off from my job for vaping in secret and now I need to go back out into the job market and interview for some new jobs. Here is my situation: I am a body builder and I have some serious biceps and triceps... all the muscles in my arms are popping. Should I be showing off these physical attributes in job interviews? I know that the broads would like to see the arms, but it's rare that you see a woman in charge of anything. I don't want to NOT get a job because some bro is jelly of my arm cannons, but at the same time he could be impressed and want to hire me because he knows I can work harder than anyone else with small arms. So the question: hide the arms or show them off; short sleeve, or long sleeve, or button down tank top? (PS, I do have some sick tats that up the market value)</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031752AAZxB2h</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:17:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I get tan?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031834AA8KvIQ</link><description>I am already tan but I have a farmer's tan and I don't want to go to my swimming classes like that. Is there anything I can do to darken my shoulders and stomach? I don't think I can use a spray tan but all other suggestions are welcome</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031834AA8KvIQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:18:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Nylon shorts or polyester vintage sport shorts in the drier.is it safe?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031917AAtgQfR</link><description>the reflective satin stuff material, the other is like a reflective windbreaker fabric.these are like vintage boxing/socccer running shorts sport shorts. Will the drier be safe to them?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031917AAtgQfR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:19:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to make dog fatter?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031927AAFMFnP</link><description>my dog is skinny even though i already add more portion to his food daily
Yes he moves a lot and i don't want him fatter because i want him to move less
he just look so fragile 
i want him fatter
any advice ? Just want to make him looks healthy
not until overweight Just want to make him looks healthy
not until overweight</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707031927AAFMFnP</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:19:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What do you think of the Amelia Earhart pic from last night's news?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032246AApahCt</link><description>Is the woman standing Islamic? Looks like she has a Hijab on. Can anyone identify the ship types? I think this is in the Philippines. The plane is in front of the first ship. There are other pics that show it. C:\Users\BRYAN\Desktop\PLANE.png http://www.cnn.com/2017/07/06/us/amelia-earhart-mystery-theories/index.html</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032246AApahCt</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:22:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Am I blood related to people of the same race as me? Even if we arent from the same family?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032352AA2QylB</link><description>My friend, who is part French, said that im her cousin because I'm also part French.. is this true?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032352AA2QylB</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My real cat left me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032352AAIgLJL</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032352AAIgLJL</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:23:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What kind of beetle is this?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032426AAT1pG0</link><description>Here's the link to the video I took of it! Please identify. 

https://instagram.com/p/BWOJkA3HcM_/</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032426AAT1pG0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:24:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone help me come up with a plot idea that takes place at the beach?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032451AA2428D</link><description>I'm not asking for a complete plot idea, just something to get me started. I have characters already; 4 teenage girls who just graduated high school in the 1960's. Genre is either drama or romance. Please help me come up with something to work with?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032451AA2428D</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:24:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What's the cheapest priced motels in Austin for daily, weekly, and monthly stays???</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032853AAM7aLg</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032853AAM7aLg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:28:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What essential oils are okay to use around pet mice?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032908AAMVNWa</link><description>I just got a mouse that I've been wanting for a very long time. I thought that I'd considered every problem and was ready for them, but as soon as I was getting ready for bed I realized I don't know anything about essential oils and mice. I always diffuse Thieves oil while I'm sleeping, but I know that cinnamon and cloves are generally bad for pets. the diffuser isn't near the cage, but it is in the same room. Is this safe for my mouse? If not, can anybody give me a list of oils that are safe to diffuse around small pets? Please no idiocy.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032908AAMVNWa</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:29:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What rhymes with divorce?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032956AAvuWek</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707032956AAvuWek</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:29:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Cockatiel mutation and sexing?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033007AA91Zy2</link><description>Mom is norm grey and dad is lutino.  Babies are pied and lutino.   What are they split and can I visually sex them?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033007AA91Zy2</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:30:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What's the cheapest priced motels in Austin for daily, weekly, and monthly stays???</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033015AARqcD0</link><description>Looking for best price motel daily,  weekly,  and monthly.... TY</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033015AARqcD0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:30:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What does this mean and should I be worried?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033119AAC0LQw</link><description>I am of age and so is my boyfriend so please don t lecture me. I am on birth control and today my boyfriend and I had sex for the firs time in about a week without a condom. He finished in me and after that I got the usual- lots of discharge and all of his ejaculate coming out. 5 hours later I went to the bathroom and wiped and looked and saw a couple streaks of red blood in a lot of thick, clear sticky discharge. Should I be worried? Why do you think I got this?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033119AAC0LQw</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:31:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: SIG p228 question?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033135AAyulqt</link><description>So, I was shooting a SIG p228, and I find it hard to push the slide release down. Also, the slide cuts my thumb pad when I release it. Is there anything I can do to help fix these problems?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033135AAyulqt</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:31:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Lutino/clear pied cockatiel?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033156AAI5kk1</link><description>I have two lutino cockatiels.  When I shine light on one of their eyes, the pupil is a burgundy red, and the other birds eyes are a light red.  Why are they different?  Is one a clear pied?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033156AAI5kk1</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:31:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is this and should I be worried?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033206AAx6Z5d</link><description>I am of age and so is my boyfriend so please don't lecture me. I am on birth control and today my boyfriend and I had sex for the firs time in about a week without a condom. He finished in me and after that I got the usual- lots of discharge and all of his ejaculate coming out. 5 hours later I went to the bathroom and wiped and looked and saw a couple streaks of red blood in a lot of thick, clear sticky discharge. Should I be worried? Why do you think I got this? I am currently feeling very nauseous but I don't know if it has any correlation to what happened today. I am having a lot of clear thick discharge</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033206AAx6Z5d</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:32:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can ab+ mother and a+ father have an ab- child?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033459AA7nmJX</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033459AA7nmJX</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:34:59 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help?! i have no female to talk to about these things :(?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033503AACOZha</link><description>i got my period at the age of ten and i'm now fourteen years old. i'm still an AA cup and my breasts haven't grown since i've gotten my first period! that's four whole years! will i ever grow? or am i stuck at an AA cup? i've heard stories of girls who's breasts didn't grow until 8-9 years after their first periods but i feel left behind because all my friends are developed and since i got my period so early doesn't that mean i'd start developing earlier? :( everyone teases me for being flat chested and i'm pudgy so why aren't my breasts growing?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033503AACOZha</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:35:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I'm always hungry?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033526AAZezki</link><description>I am constantly hungry. I don't remember the last time I felt full. I'm not pregnant, I'm still a virgin. I just eat and eat and eat, but I don't gain any weight?! It's so weird! What is going on? I'm 20 I probably exercise once a week, which isn't a lot at all, and I admit I don't hydrate as often as I should</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033526AAZezki</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:35:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Michigan ar15 hunting?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033535AA7WmUc</link><description>I was wondering if you could legally hunt a turkey with a 556 or 223 ar15. It is the only rifle I have that I could take hunting and I want to know if it is legal.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033535AA7WmUc</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:35:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who sells the best brand of liquid lipstick?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033610AAC0fZk</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033610AAC0fZk</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:36:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What should I name my story character?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033851AAYpCt0</link><description>Okay, so first of all, she's going to be 15-17 years old (I haven't decided yet but I know she's going to be having a birthday soon.) She dyed her hair a shiny silver tint and has light brown eyes. She isn't popular, and doesn't have many friends. Not from being shy or anything, she always speaks her mind and just doesn't care for too many friends. She's tall and pretty slim. I hope that's enough information. Also, if you have any ideas of how I should alter her appearance or something, let me know. Thanks &#10084;&#65039;</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033851AAYpCt0</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:38:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a kyphotic lordotic posture I'm trying to fix.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033928AAqxLBC</link><description>My question is how many inches taller can I get when I fix it. I read that bad posture can make you up to 2 inches shorter. Will I get 2 inches taller? It got so bad I cannot stand up straight</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707033928AAqxLBC</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:39:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is my diet ok for a 15 year old girl?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034017AAIBGR5</link><description>I'm 158cm tall &amp; weigh 48.5kg. I'm kinda trying to get down to around 45kg (maybe less). I know I'm a healthy weight but I have quite a lot of fat on me. Lately I've been avoiding certain foods more than usual and feeling a bit guilty after eating them. I feel totally fine but am worried that if I don't eat enough I'll harm myself in the long run. At the same time, though I feel kinda bad about myself if I eat over like 1250 calories. I've just generally been stressing about food &amp; calories &amp; stuff quite a bit lately &amp; would like some opinions on my diet.

Breakfast: 45g of cereal with a bit of milk or scrambled eggs on a piece of toast (200-ish calories)
Lunch: a super grains bar (115 calories) or a banana (100-ish calories) or a piece of toast with peanut butter ( 180-ish calories)
Tea: about 1/2 a 9" plate of stirfry/roast vegetables, 1/4 of beans &amp; some kind of vegetarian meat or 1/4 of potato/kumara (450/500-ish calories) or bulgur wheat salad (400-ish calories)
Snack: a green apple/a kiwifruit &amp; like 5 pecans/almonds (150-ish calories)
The calories might be way off since I don't measure everything, I just make an educated guess.

I rock climb 1-3 times a week &amp; take at least 5000 steps most days btw (:</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034017AAIBGR5</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:40:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What are some villain/monster like powers I could give to my main character?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034148AAI9hHV</link><description>My main character lived in fear most of her life believing she was dangerous and going to hurt the people she loved because these sick twisted thoughts would pop inside her head of her being this murderous evil crazy person. She found out she had OCD and finally felt free from her fears until she was given immortality and gained a supernatural gift to go with it. 

At first I thought of giving her a gift that with one touch she could heal all mental or psychical illnesses and make people extremely. Her hands could also push away attacks from others and sense danger. 

I like that gift, but I think I want to give her a little more conflict then that. I want her gift to be very dark and harmful, and she fears it and refuses to use it, but struggles to control it at times. Kind of like frozen with Elsa's power, but I don't want her to have ice powers. 

Any suggestions?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034148AAI9hHV</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:41:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: 8th grade makeup advice?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034205AAKT4zX</link><description>i m going into 8th grade, and i need some advice on what kind of makeup to get. i am mostly looking for foundation, since i used BB cream in 7th grade (may or may not stick to this). i really want a step up from that though. does anybody know of any good foundations, that a 14 year old girl should use? not too expensive, because i don t want to spend all my money on makeup. i am planning on asking an employee at Ulta or Sephora, but i wanted another s opinion as well.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034205AAKT4zX</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:42:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: WHAT SHOULD I DO ABOUT MY BUDGIE?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034249AAzQEWR</link><description>Today I found my bird at the bottom of his cage . He couldn t move his legs so I took him to the vet and she said it has something to possibly do with a tumor and it was nothing she could do but she gave us some polyoma for inflammation and pain . Idk what he had exactly though . She said she s sure he isn t going to make it but I don t want to give up just yet because he s moving and trying . But I don t want him to suffer . What should I do ?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034249AAzQEWR</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:42:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Prime rib or sliced chateubriand?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034257AADoZVY</link><description>Need help picking between these 2 for my wedding menu.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034257AADoZVY</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:42:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Tingling/Numb in my fingertips, legs, feet?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034331AAZeAFU</link><description>So I pop my knees &amp; fingers &amp; basically anything on my body all the time, it's just a habit of mine. anyways I have been getting in the habit of popping my knees a lot so much that I will try to force it ( I'm an idiot ) &amp; the other day I tried &amp; it became sore &amp; kept getting more sore so I thought maybe I just made it sore from doing it so much, but my knee still hurts &amp; feels absolutely weird like a tight feeling &amp; it's swollen, AND last night I just started to feel tingling in my leg, then it went to my feet. Both of them then eventually my fingertips felt numb &amp; I thought it would be gone by the morning but nope. Still happening. &amp; all day at work my legs &amp; feet would be numb &amp; tingling. What do you think I have done? Do you think it has to do with hurting my knee? Help me!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034331AAZeAFU</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Mom says yes to pain pills, dad says no. mom says why not? dad says they are addicting.mom says, then why do they make them? dad ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034521AA1zMGQ</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034521AA1zMGQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:45:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: So I work with kids and I ve had atleast 3 kids insult me and call me fat out of nowhere i personally don t think I am but it s not the best?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034729AAhK1Wu</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034729AAhK1Wu</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:47:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have depressed/suicidal friend?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034740AAIOrdF</link><description>I have a friend (She is a girl) who I met in second grade. Back then she was happy. She went to another school and we lost touch. Then we met at a birthday party. She now now goes to my school and we text. She is depressed. Her parents are separated. She is too scared to go to anyone else but me. She says her parents get mad when they see the cuts on her wrist.(Its not an abusive home as far as I know). She wants too see a therapist but she doesn't want to ask. At one point she said im not suicidal but God can take me. It really scared me. Today she said she is suicidal. She refuses to talk to her parents. I need help. I can't loose a great friend.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034740AAIOrdF</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:47:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do I feel get sudden feelings of needing to eat but when I do eat I get full after 3-4 bites?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034832AAYbfR6</link><description>I am 20, I am fit and I know I have a good metabolism but during the day I get sudden feelings that feel like a kick in the stomach and I need to eat or I m going to throw up, but when I do eat I get full after 3-4 bites. This is worst at night when I lay down I get a sudden feeling of nausea that feels like I need to eat, I usually ignore it at night if I can but I m just wondering if this is a symptom of something or is there something I m doing wrong? I feel like I m not eating enough but if I try to eat a big meal it makes me feel sick as well... help???</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707034832AAYbfR6</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:48:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How does the muscular system and respiratory system work together to maintain body temperature?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035326AAp6wyK</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035326AAp6wyK</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:53:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I feel like I am not bonding with my guinea pig well. I pick him up and reach in his cage a lot. What do I do?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035528AAFDW8B</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035528AAFDW8B</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:55:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is a rabbit good for me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035610AAFTXaA</link><description>My friend has baby bunnies and I want to get one but I want to know if I would be a good fit. I'm soon to be 18 and still in high school and going to live with my patents until after college (Gonna be a vet tech). I've had rabbits before when I was younger but none for a few years. I would get a cage for it to go in when I'm not not (for school or work) and night but when I'm home it would be able to run around in the "fence" I would buy. The cage would not be a tiny one it would have enough room to lay down and it would be tall enough for it to stand up. I would make sure it had at least two hours a day of being able to run around. It would have as much as possible like all night after school if I don't work and also much of the time on the weekends and also if my brothers decide to play with it if they want when I'm not home. I also have two dogs and a cat but the dogs would never be alone with it even when it's in the cage. No small children in the house. We're all over 13 and I would do my research to make sure it had the proper food and toys and such but I just want to know if it would be okay with being in the cage. It would be given attention and I'd litter train it. Also would get it fixed when the times comes. I'm also up for recommendations on what to get and some tips on care. It would be more than a month before I get it so I have plenty of time to prepare.  Would it be okay? Thanks!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035610AAFTXaA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:56:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Loose fat fast?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035933AA4HUXr</link><description>I'm going to a pool party next week and I have lots of fat in my stomach area, any ideas on how to loose fat fast in a week?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035933AA4HUXr</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:59:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My daughter is abusive and I think has a mental/emotional disorder. I can't deal with it anymore, what do I do???</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035948AAYWhzh</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707035948AAYWhzh</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 04:59:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why do fans applaud players for taking less money?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040015AArVBzg</link><description>When in reality all they're doing is sacrificing millions to help the billionaire owner save money? The NBA a soft cap which means owners can go over if they're fine with paying the luxury tax. Players like Dirk continue to take less and have nothing to show for it.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040015AArVBzg</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 05:00:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When and where does Auburn play Kentucky in football again?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040124AArFQ0h</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040124AArFQ0h</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 05:01:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hands feet and mouth?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040519AAeFXgN</link><description>My daughter was diagnosed with hands feet and mouth disease today. She hasn't had a fever since 5:00 this morning. I was wondering bout how long she would be contagious for.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707040519AAeFXgN</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 05:05:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone stop Booker T from saying "MMMMMMM!!" every time a wrestler punches his opponent?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170711031316AAcBWD0</link><description>it really annoys me!!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170711031316AAcBWD0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2017 04:13:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why is my a/c unit freezing?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170711234513AAr8ieX</link><description>If the temp outside is 90 &amp; up, I figured that if the thermostat was set to 75 it should be enough to cool the house without the unit freezing. (We were previously told by the landlord that keeping it set to 70 "doesn t give the heat pump enough of a rest") The freezing seems to happen no matter what we set thermostat to &amp; 75 is about as high as we can stand it. Filter is new, no furniture is near the thermostat, nothing appears to be wrong with the unit outside (other than the ice), we are not contstantly fussing with the thermostat. What are we doing wrong here?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170711234513AAr8ieX</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 00:45:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: If Colombus was really here first then why do Mexicans speak Spanish?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170712200436AAEDVN0</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170712200436AAEDVN0</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2017 21:04:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do I have allergies?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192310AAv4trn</link><description>I some times get this thing in my lungs and throat that makes me need to clear my throat.  I take allergy pills, but they sometimes do not work. (But it gets a lot better when I take the pills.) I seem to need them year around. I do have Dogs/Cats, and I have grown up with them.  There are a few times when I have been away from them for a while, and I still have the tickle.  It sometimes gets worse when I get done Coughing, and after I eat/drink. Sometimes, out of no where, my throat gets this really bad dry tickle that makes me cough.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192310AAv4trn</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:23:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How skinny is 220 pounds if 7'1 for a basketball player and what kind of diet / mealplan do you suggest in order to put on weight and muscle?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192810AAFVwkh</link><description>https://tallguysfree.com/i/upload/2017/06/11/20170611221522-c473df57-xl.jpg</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192810AAFVwkh</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:28:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Houston vs Dallas?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192834AA2L9ns</link><description>Which city has better job markets, entertainment/things to do, nightlife, and architecture/skyline?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192834AA2L9ns</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How much weight can I expect to lose on a juice fast?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192911AAh4hLX</link><description>Hi, I'm looking into a juice fast to lose weight and I was wondering how much weight I can lose if I fast for 6+ months. I  also heard that juice fasting is especially good becHi, I'm looking into a juice fast to lose weight and I was wondering how much weight I can lose if I fast for 6+ months. I  also heard that juice fasting is especially good because it helps get rid of all the toxins in your body. Thanks!ause it helps get rid of all the toxins in your body. Thanks!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170713192911AAh4hLX</guid><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:29:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why cannot download the chinese keyboard on samsung?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170714130453AAv0Uye</link><description>All the other keyboards except of mandarin related keyboard will download. This is annoying me so much I can't talk to my friends or type anything in chinese. If I don't get any help I will try to reset my phone to factory settings. I tried getting help from samsung and they did nothing. Because my phone forced me to update, i can't get into my we chat account. It is driving me crazy!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170714130453AAv0Uye</guid><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2017 14:04:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do you realize the trolls are moving your philosophy questions?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170716134319AApp7tR</link><description>They still say philosophy at the top, but they don't show on the list. Meanwhile THEIR questions appear on the list but inside they say "golf" or whatever so you can't move them by just moving them. If you move your Q to another category and then BACK to philosophy they appear on the list again. 

What is the philosophy of killing/moving this question every ten minutes?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170716134319AApp7tR</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 14:43:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are people here as guilty as those in Horoscopes, for imposing their belief/perception as answer?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170716175108AAEhHjw</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170716175108AAEhHjw</guid><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2017 18:51:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: As an Australian Infidel have you ever fallen victim to "Tiquyya"?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717032203AAAE7HO</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717032203AAAE7HO</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 04:22:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: This cut is four days old. Shouldn't it look better than this?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717041253AAhhPdg</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717041253AAhhPdg</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 05:12:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Poll: How important is money?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717053924AAqEoXS</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717053924AAqEoXS</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 06:39:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Since this was a nazi eagle, would it be offensive to get tattooed even though in the picture, there is no swastika. Just need an opinion?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717054857AAqRcZU</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717054857AAqRcZU</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 06:48:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I stop chronic masturbation ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717073044AAtRKgH</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717073044AAtRKgH</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 08:30:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: New lab puppy.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717200246AAmiE9Z</link><description>Hey I m getting a Labrador puppy soon. Any tips for the first couple of days? Also my family has a five seater car and even though we don t travel too often, we sometimes would go to Donegal to visit family and wouldn t want to leave the dog at home. would it be safe to carry a puppy (and later a fully grown dog) in our laps? (In the back seat).

I'm just pretty nervous to get a new pup. I have found a breeder from recommendation of an uncle who breeds another dog breed, but when looking at the litter what should I do to check if the pup I like is healthy? My parents have all the stuff for the dog it was just a matter of fitting everything. And the reason I ask about how to know if the pup is healthy is becuase for a while now after look up about puppy mills I'm anxious that I would be getting a puppy mill dog even though I have met the breeders and my dad knows them on recommendation of another quality breeder Oh sorry forgot to mention we are a five person family</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170717200246AAmiE9Z</guid><pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2017 21:02:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is there a way to sneak pads to the bathroom during class?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718002755AAv5rIM</link><description>I'm going into 8th grade and I started my period on the last day of school. School is coming up and I was wondering if there was a way to sneak pads to the bathroom without anyone knowing also is there a way to open the pad without the loud crakle noise??</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718002755AAv5rIM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 01:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have a question about portable air conditioning units.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718002755AAsai4g</link><description>Can anyone tell me what the reason for the ventilation tube is on portable ac's? Do they drip a lot or release a lot of moisture through the vent hose? I don't believe they do but my house mate believes they use the tube to expel water. I read that most evaporate the water these days. Anyone know for certain?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718002755AAsai4g</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 01:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can gorillas use the internet?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718005152AAQDsjF</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718005152AAQDsjF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 01:51:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How many Advil PM 200 mg pills would kill me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718022249AAr1o2z</link><description>Don't care about the damage, just care about what would do the trick. I'm just asking for innocent curiosity reasons &amp; not suicidal. Seriously just curious. Please be precise. It would suck to do damage and not do the trick. Weight is around 107lb. This is just for pure curiosity..Thanks for answering. I just need an accurate answer please guys. Help me out This is for a school thing. Like 20 pills? 30 pills? 40 pills? Anyone have an accurate dosage calculation for a 107lb female? Thanks. I'm sorry you went through that marybeth. I just want to know the exact measurement seriously for a school thing. Please can someone just tell me. I can't find anything on the internet. Damage but not dying sucks even more if this person in the story yeah..It's a school thing guys. PLEASE JUST FREAKIN TELL ME HOW MANY! I know people die from this so what is the dose?????? How many blood pressure pills? How would I get that? Someone in my family has those pills I guess, but they would find out...This is a school story..Writing a possible realistic scenario for a story thing..</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718022249AAr1o2z</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 03:22:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will gorilla glue or faller plastic cement work better on my VCR's FacePlate?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718031948AAMn7iD</link><description>It fell off the nightstand and landed on the concrete and the corner cracked. No missing pieces or anything just that corner cracked open. 
help?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718031948AAMn7iD</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 04:19:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do people use flushable cat litter? Do they sift it and only flush the poop or put an amount of litter in the toliet? How much litter?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718035751AAAyzZL</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718035751AAAyzZL</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 04:57:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where to buy tires to flip for weight training?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718040303AAodvSk</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718040303AAodvSk</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:03:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can a male still growth penis size in the 20-21 years of age?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718041946AAaLRzN</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718041946AAaLRzN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:19:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who was best actor to portray Hitler?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042505AAnA6LU</link><description>Specifically, not the best actor per se, but the actor who gave the best and most convincing portrayal of Hitler. I like the Charlie Chaplin answer! There was also a dog in Sweden that was trained to do the Hitler salute, and Hitler himself put a bounty on it... true story! I've seen some good portrayals, but having heard the OSS recordings of Hitler discussing strategy, very cool and calculated, it seems few actors really capture this. Rather than an angry madman, though he was a sick and twisted man, he was very cool and calculating.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042505AAnA6LU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:25:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the meaning of life?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042525AAt6Z4L</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042525AAt6Z4L</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:25:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help! my jaw hurts?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042529AASTclW</link><description>the left side of my jaw hurts near the ear when i try to close my mouth completely. I'm thinking about seeing a dentist.... should i be concerned? has anyone experienced this before? if so what did u do and how did u fix it?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042529AASTclW</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:25:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What do I need to care for basic aquarium plants?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042820AAvsRJ4</link><description>I'm planning to add some live plants to my betta fish's tank and I want to know what supplies I need. I'm planning to put common plants like java fern, amazon sword, java moss, anubias, maybe some duckweed etc. I don't like how it looks potted so I was going to plant it in sand. What's the bare minimum I need to care for the plants? Also, how do I trim amazon sword plants? I heard they tend to get really big</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718042820AAvsRJ4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:28:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are you ready to meet your maker?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718043121AAAxzj6</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718043121AAAxzj6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:31:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Hidden tattoo vs Jobs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718043433AADxybH</link><description>I'm 16 and getting a tattoo on my stomach where I can hide it and it would only be seen if I was wearing a bathing costume. Do I even have to tell the people I will be working for in the future I have it if they can't see it?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718043433AADxybH</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:34:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is that cotton like substance growing up under the foreskin?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044225AA8603U</link><description>Son 12 has a cotton like substance under his foreskin. What is it? Why is there? Asked his dad and he has no idea. Son always washes well and has learned to pull his foreskin when her pees, etc. Help!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044225AA8603U</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:42:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have different answers. I would love to hear your answer in a one succinct paragraph?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044331AAC05vh</link><description>Two people return to their long neglected garden and find among the weeds a few of the old plants surprisingly vigorous. One says to the other, "It must be that a gardener has been coming and doing something about these plants.&#8221; Upon inquiry they find that no neighbor has ever seen anyone at work in their garden. The first man says to the other, "He must have worked while people slept." The other says, "No, someone would have heard him and besides, anybody who cared about the plants would have kept down these weeds." The first man says, "Look at the way these are arranged. There is purpose and a feeling for beauty here. I believe that someone comes, someone invisible to mortal eyes. I believe that the more carefully we look the more we shall find confirmation of this." 
They examine the garden ever so carefully and sometimes they come on new things suggesting that a gardener comes and sometimes they come on new things suggesting the contrary and even that a malicious person has been at work. Besides examining the garden carefully, they also study what happens to gardens left without attention. Each learns all the other learns about this and about the garden. 
Consequently, when after all this, one says, "I still believe a gardener comes," while the other says, "I don't,"
	
What is the difference between them?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044331AAC05vh</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:43:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Health question? Help!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044600AAH27F7</link><description>I have tooth pain (the whole set teeth, my stomach hurts, I have diarrhea, a saliva gland stone, a canker sore, and plaque on my teeth, ive been brushing morning and night, could it be that the tooth paste is making them sensitive? Or cavities? Whats wrong with my body? Help!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044600AAH27F7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:46:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do I check original solitaire?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044629AAKG6Rq</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044629AAKG6Rq</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:46:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is negative equilibrium?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044728AAqNPxM</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718044728AAqNPxM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:47:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Best vitamins/ supplements for migraines?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045027AACYXST</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045027AACYXST</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:50:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can this grey mold harm me?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045502AAsSFW4</link><description>I was looking in my recycling been for cans, and found an old Guinness can. I always wanted to know what he ball inside of the can looked like. So I cut it open and all of a sudden grey fumes which I assume are spores came out like smoke. I looked inside to see what it was and there was a large clump of grey mold. Once I figured that out I threw it away immediately. I unfortunately breathed in a fair amount of "fumes". How screwed am I and how can I prevent myself from getting sick or hopefully not kick the mediforical bucket?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045502AAsSFW4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:55:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Microperforate hymen?? please help!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045712AANLs03</link><description>ok so im 14 &amp; a virgin. i wanted to use tampons but relliazed i couldn't see a hole in my vagina.. i've had my period for 4 years and all the blood comes out normally. so why dont i have an opeing i think i may have Microperforate hymen. but blood comes out fine... is this ok to live with or do you HAVE to get medical help or can i live with it?? IF YOU DONT KNOW WHAT MICROPERFORATE HYMEN IS PLEASE GOOGLE IT THERES JUST THE TINEST LITTLE HOLE IN THE VERY VERY BACK OF MY VAGINA OR WHATEVER. 
AND ITS HALF WAY COVERED BY SKIN NOT ALL THE WAY BUT ALMOST ACTUALLY I THINK I COULD HAVE Septate hymen CAUSE IN THE VERY VERY BACK OF MY VAGINA IS A TINY TINY HOLE THAT LOOKS LIKE 2 HOLES BECUASE THERES A PIECE OF SKIN COVERING THE HOLE MAKING IT LOOK LIKE 2 HOLES</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718045712AANLs03</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 05:57:12 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Weight loss in 6 weeks?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718050224AAV4hDO</link><description>I currently weigh 140 and am 5 5 female 20 years old. I go to the gym 3 days a week for weight lifting and 2 days of cardio. I also plan to incorporate a healthy diet. I go back to college in 6 weeks and would love to look slightly different aka skinnier and more toned. How different can I look in 6 weeks?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718050224AAV4hDO</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:02:24 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can sex be a treatment for depression?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718050427AAUofEA</link><description>I did really poorly in school last year.  And I am scared of the new year starting in a couple months.  Can sex help me feel better? I don't have a boyfriend but that shouldn't really matter</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718050427AAUofEA</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:04:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do You Like The Beatles?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051354AAQnFQ6</link><description>I'm writing this fanfiction on Wattpad that I just published yesterday. I'm not finished yet, but I think you should check it out. It's called "Yesterday (A Beatles Fanfiction)". My username is RockingHorsePerson.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051354AAQnFQ6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:13:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to get over fear of failure?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051542AAGpdPq</link><description>This probably sounds stupid, but I have a pretty severe fear of failure. It's affecting my school and athletic performance (especially school). For example, whenever test results are posted, I get anxiety attacks and start to shake uncontrollably. I don't know what's wrong with me! AP Exam results came out two weeks ago, and I still haven't checked mine because whenever I get the courage to do so, I get dizzy and nauseous. I'm a runner, and before every competitive race I throw up because I'm too scared to commit to it! I don't know why I get triggered like this (I also have bipolar). Does anyone else have the same fear? Idk what to do, this fear is taking over my life</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051542AAGpdPq</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:15:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Yesterday, some of the buttons on my microwave were not working and today they are working fine. Does that mean there is a short in it?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051646AAYORnr</link><description>Should I be worried about it being a fire hazard?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051646AAYORnr</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:16:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: In five-men soccer, how many men on each team are allowed to be on the field at any given time?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051905AAqi0FS</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051905AAqi0FS</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:19:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Staubach, Aikman, Meredith, Romo, White or Dak?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051940AA6Etz7</link><description>or Quincy Carter?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718051940AA6Etz7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:19:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How will the GST affect gold jewellery?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052421AAHYhHD</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052421AAHYhHD</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:24:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help with my diet, not sure it's the most healthy?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052834AADFXzr</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052834AADFXzr</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:28:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When weight lifting does higher weight lower reps or lower weight higher reps build muscle faster?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052914AAo1NGo</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052914AAo1NGo</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:29:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How to care for our new kitty?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052958AAeATAC</link><description>About a week ago my boyfriend and I found a cat laying in the middle of the road, presumably hit by a car. My boyfriend has had a couple of pets killed by cars, and now as a result he moves roadkill animals off the road so no pet owner has to deal with the headache of scraping their pet off the pavement the way he has. However when he got out to move this kitty he was still alive. Unable to afford the vet bill, we took him to the overnight drop box at out local shelter and came back to see if he made it the next day. Now a week later he's bounced back and can walk, run,  jump, and eat on his own. The girls at the shelter have been asking us about adopting him and we think it's a lovely idea. However, the damage done to him after getting hit has left him with a head tilt. Because of this we've affectionately given him the name Wybie, after the little boy from the movie Coraline who walk around with his head tilted to the side like our kitty. He can walk, run, and jump, but he can't do it straight. How can we care for our little Wybie the best we can given his disability?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718052958AAeATAC</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:29:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will my four day period get longer when I start birth control?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053013AAyfF5i</link><description>I'm starting bc pills pretty soon and I'm aware of what could happen to me but I was thinking because the sugar pills is 7 days would my period be 7 days ifs it's four while I'm not on the pill?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053013AAyfF5i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:30:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I ve been on birth control almost a year and me and my boyfriend have been having unprotected sex (no condom) for about 2 months amipregnant?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053036AAf0KCt</link><description>I m pretty good about taking my birth control but one time I forgot to take one pill but took it as soon as I remembered the next day. I also sometimes take it an hour early or few hours late. It s ortho tri cyclen. He never ejaculates in me he always pulls out however my stomach has been super gurgely and I haven t been able to poop that much lately and I heard that s an early sign of pregnancy. I don t have any other symptoms though and I m not supposed to get my period for another week or so. I m terrified and I just want an opinion on if you think I am pregnant.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053036AAf0KCt</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I have no motivation and it is destroying my life.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053036AAWyRSW</link><description>I can't find the motivation to do anything. I'm 21 years old, and I work as a bus Person at a restaurant 30 hours a week. I've had the owner of a car business tell me that I can call him whenever I want if I want work, and I can never motivate myself to call him. I can't even motivate myself to do my laundry or clean my apartment half the time. All I ever want to do is drink, play video games. I've lost interest in guitar playing, one of my strings broke and I can't bring myself to drive to the music store and buy new strings, the only thing I ever spend my money on is beer almost every night. My dad rides me all the time about how I never do anything except drink and sit on the computer. I realize that these are all problems but I can't bring myself to fix them. My dad thinks it's just because I'm a lazy piece of you know what. I told him the I would kill him, and of course I didn't actually mean it, I was just mad at the time I don't actually want to kill him and he pretty much resents me now. He told me that if my other 2 brothers stopped talking to him it would bother him, but if I stopped talking to him it wouldn't bother him one bit. I don't think it's because I'm lazy I think they're more deep rooted issues that are going on with me, and I don't know what to do. I'm considering seeking professional help, I don't know whether to do outpatient therapy or impatient. My lifestyle right now has become unmanageable and I need help.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053036AAWyRSW</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:30:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When does most tooth movement occur?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053102AAKgISx</link><description>my orthodontist appointments are spread out in six weeks, so when does the tooth move the most?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053102AAKgISx</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:31:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Garden: Do you have an organic home made recipe for white flies on tomato plants? Thanks.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053207AADz6kR</link><description>Please, no dish soap. It is petroleum base.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053207AADz6kR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:32:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How long do you think I will need braces for?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053308AACsKjI</link><description>http://i1082.photobucket.com/albums/j377/smoothiebanana/Mobile%20Uploads/20170718_013043_zpszqpbrfvs.jpg</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053308AACsKjI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:33:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can someone help me understand a healthier diet?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053326AA7w7U0</link><description>Ok so I was 150 pounds and I am 5'8. I'm a little chubbier then I want to be so I started to try to diet. I never really knew how many calories I was consuming but I tried to do a 1,100 calorie diet with low carbs (and I guess fat as well) I've been using the app myfitnesspal to track my foods for the days. So far, I have lost 6 pounds however I'm not seeing much changes in my body. The real problem here is I have a limit (on the app) of 97g of carbs a day and 37g of fat a day. I'm doing good with my protein and staying under these is just fine for me. However, I'm not reaching my 1,100 calories for the day !! I thought it would be hard to consume so little calories but turns out I'm not getting enough. I don't think this is healthy to consume too little and I'm afraid I'm going to start losing body fat. I'm also a vegetarian so what should I do?? Are the amount of carbs and fat I'm getting a day healthy as well? (Sorry for the lengthy paragraph)</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053326AA7w7U0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:33:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is a good amount of calories to consume ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053435AALm7S7</link><description>I'm chubby , trying to lose a little stomach fat but also trying to gain muscle. I see girls on instagram doing 2,500 calories a day and saying more is better. I've been doing 1,100 a day , so what really is the right way?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053435AALm7S7</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:34:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I'm moving soon and will have to use a community basketball court?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053534AAAhEwN</link><description>Im not gonna be able to play in my driveway any more once I move. I know most of the time I'm going to want to play by myself. Just wondering if there is anyone else who has to use a outdoor community court and what time you go so there is no people and how often is there games going on exc.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053534AAAhEwN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:35:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I got my tongue pierced on July 8th. it s isn t swollen, don t hurt, little puss. but this part... what is it. help.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053741AAWR28e</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053741AAWR28e</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:37:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is it okay to take Claritin after Benadryl?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053748AAFg5Or</link><description>I took a Benadryl about 2 1/2 hours ago but it barely helped, and my allergies were so bad tonight, so I took a Claritin as well. Will I be okay, or will this cause major side affects?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053748AAFg5Or</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:37:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Would you have a testicle removed if it was causing so much pain it interfered with daily living?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053839AA9Siq5</link><description>Say you had an injury that caused you to have pain in one of your testicles that equated to someone flicking it every 10 minutes. You have had many procedures and several operations to repair the damage to the point where it is now just a useless painful "ball" in your sac. You are on pain medication which works most of the time but you will always regret lifting something heavy, most exercises, and all  but very gentle sex.The only thing left is to have it removed BUT the doctors give you a 50/50 chance that the pain will continue as "ghost pain" and nothing further could be done. Would you have a painful testicle removed if you will have a 50% chance that the pain would still be there? 
After 4 failed operations and numerous procedures would you still do it knowing your chances of pain relief are nothing better than a role of the dice, that ghost pains would still cripple you, or 
 worse?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718053839AA9Siq5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:38:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are my vag nerves damaged?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054157AA4N6GE</link><description>I use to vibrate my clit when I was virgin. The had sex and I'm 18- so far have had sex w 4 guys since losing my virginity at 16... I get like this natural cream but not wet how it should be and my body can't feel horny and I've never felt pleasure while having sex. I've only once felt horny in 6 grade when my best friend was teaching me how to kiss. Any tips how to get the nerves back, make my self feel horny, get wet and make sex feel pleasureable? Don't tell me "u haven't found the right guy" that's wrong. Even if I wanna feel horny, I just can't . sucks. I've never felt how sex felt....</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054157AA4N6GE</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:41:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the pag ibig mid no. of allan demain?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054252AAvLJyS</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054252AAvLJyS</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:42:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Red/pink dots on arm that sometimes itch?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054411AAS6ZNZ</link><description>When my palm is facing up, about 3 inches from my wrist, are two tiny red dots. I've had them for as long as I can remember. Half of the time, they are flat, not raised at all. (Each dot has no more than a 2 millimetre diameter.) Sometimes, one dot (or both) raise and itch. They are spaced about 2 millimetres apart. I'm 13, and I've always had them. I can remember them being there years and years ago. I'm healthy, and not on any kind of medication. When the dots are not raised, they just look like I took a salmon-coloured marker and put two dots on my arm. What are these two mysterious pink/red dots? Are they harmless?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054411AAS6ZNZ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:44:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How can I fix my frizzy hair?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054530AAZjyms</link><description>I'm starting a job as a Flight Attendant, and my hair needs serious help. It's thick, and naturally is semi-wavy. But the Frizz! Oh my gosh, the FRIZZ! Especially on top.

 I wash my hair every 2-3 days, and towel/ air dry. I just use your everyday, run-of-the-mill shampoo and conditioner. 

Ideally, I would love to get rid of the frizz, embrace the natural beach waves, and make it shinier. But if nothing else, the frizziness.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054530AAZjyms</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:45:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Nipples are sore! I'm a virgin and have already had my period. I'm 23, could my boobs be growing?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054757AAlqCuj</link><description>I swear my boobs never developed in the first place, they're gross a cups. My nipples have been sore for a few days, just the nipples and they seem more bouncy. I'm hoping they're somehow finally growing, even though I think they stop at 17, maybe I'm a late late bloomer!?? Anyone have any experience with getting a bigger chest later in life? I'm a virgin, not pregnant and I've already had my period so it isn't premestraul. I know it's a lot to want but I've really never felt like a real woman. Any thoughts? I'll turn 23 next month.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054757AAlqCuj</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:47:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is this intriguing for the start of a book? (Without knowing anything)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054840AAD2re1</link><description>When she inhaled, she tasted the blood gushing from her upper lip, but she swallowed it, and kept walking down the dark alleyway, clutching the tiny piece of paper in her fingertips.
	&#8220;718 Ash Street,&#8221; she whispered, and flinched as she spoke to herself.
	She coughed- more blood, but she ignored it, and navigated around the broken glass on the sidewalk. Her designer heels were long gone, ditched at least five miles ago. The train of her long silver gown trailed on the ground, the tulle  completely tattered and blackened from dirt. The thin material of the silk waist flapped open, exposing her bruised stomach. Her hyperventilating quickened with the headlights of each passing car, as she ducked in the shadows to stay hidden.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718054840AAD2re1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:48:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where I can buy cheap jerseys?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055055AAo9q2J</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055055AAo9q2J</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:50:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Frequent diarrhea bathroom trips (especially right after eating)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055107AATetgt</link><description>I apologize for the gross and personal nature of this post, but I ve searched everywhere and can t seem to find an answer.

I had my gallbladder removed about four years ago, and ever since then, I ve had to go to the bathroom urgently and do my business (which usually ends up in small amounts of diarrhea). Even now, right after eating, or even in the middle of eating, I get the urge to go, and when I do it s a small amount of diarrhea.

I do not have any abdominal pain, fever, or any other symptoms. It doesn t matter what I eat, everything makes me feel this way. I do not take laxatives, I m not allergic to anything, and do not have any other symptoms besides what I stated before. Should I go to a doctor, or is an uncommon side effect that I shouldn t worry about? Are there any ideas how I can lighten the frequency, or make it stop altogether?

Side note - I do have "solid" bathroom trips, but only when I eat a lot of meat. Not sure if that helps or not.

Thank you to all who help with this, or have similar experiences</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055107AATetgt</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:51:07 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: I've had an 8 hour erection?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055620AAvZU0i</link><description>It hurts like a b*tch. I saw my wife from behind earlier, for only a second mind you, and it was enough to set me off. She tried to off me later, but it was painful to do even that, and it hurts like a motherf*cker. I'm 18 by the way, so I don't know why I'm having this. It's not like I'm an old d*ck with erectile dysfunction. I should note that my wife and I have been married since last October, and we've gone at it almost every night since. Max Hoopla. Read the description. My wife set me off, and I was up for almost 10 straight hours. After she offed me (which was, for the first time ever, painful), it hurt even worse. It was after I was up for 10 minutes, but after she did that, I was up for another 9 hours and 26 minutes. Not even joking. 

I'm all right now, and my wife and I are planning on taking a couple nights off- and then I'm bedding her like never before. Friday's gonna rock. I won't "break up with her." This isn't a high school relationship. I believe in commitment, not date the first person you get the chance to.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055620AAvZU0i</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:56:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: When to have your first cheat meal?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AAuiE3h</link><description>So I started a diet + workout, and I am planning to have my cheat meal after total of 10 days of diet and working out

is this OK?

When do people usually have the first cheat meal?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055800AAuiE3h</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:58:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do you think I could be a foreign host?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055829AA5Rk6s</link><description>I'm a young guy who's barely in my twenties, and I was thinking of learning Japanese, and to start living my life in Japan once I'm fluent. To begin my dreams of living in Japan, I thought about starting off as a host at a host club. In Japan, it's not uncommon for Japanese women to pay guys huge sums of money for a couple of cocktails and a few hours of platonic companionship. The key is to be attractive, and to lure in women. I think I have an advantage because I'm foreign. However, to be honest, I'm not the greatest at picking up women because I'm introverted, but I could still make it possible for women to enjoy my presence, since I never had trouble in that area. A description about myself, I'm half French and half Mexican, so I have black hair, but somewhat tanned skin (hazel eyes). I have a swimmer's built, and quite skinny, but I have good muscular definition. I have a youthful face, so I look younger than my real age. As for my overall appearance towards women, I have had two or three random women come to my job just to see me in the past. Anyways, it's not an ideal job (hosting and all), but I think it's better than the other typical jobs as a foreigner (like teaching English to a classroom full of people).</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055829AA5Rk6s</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:58:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ User Profiles ] Open Question : 4-12 alphanumerical usernames?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055833AA49BUd</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055833AA49BUd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:58:33 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Politics ] Open Question : Trump told White House staffers to lawyer up, but that Trump's not paying for it. Then he used campaign donations to hire lawyer's for Jr.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055850AAVtuDn</link><description>Is this part of why staffers keep leaking information? Because they know Trump will break the law, but will never help his staff? http://www.politico.com/story/2017/07/15/trump-campaign-paid-jr-attorney-240592 It is proven / public record.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055850AAVtuDn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:58:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Pregnancy ] Open Question : Could I be pregnant?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055906AAFwRTR</link><description>Me and my bf had sex 3 days before my period, the condom broke and he immediately pulled out. I was supposed to start my period on Friday (7/14) and I started taking my birth control pills on Sunday (7/16). I m now 3 days late for my period.. Could I be pregnant?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055906AAFwRTR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:59:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What's your favorite type of allergy medicine?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055928AA41GNB</link><description>Also, do you like watching paint dry?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055928AA41GNB</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:59:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Religion &amp; Spirituality ] Open Question : Christians now that yahoo answers is broken can you be honest?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055944AAQVhxN</link><description>On some level you know that Jesus is made up, why not admit it?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055944AAQVhxN</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:59:44 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Feeling like my friend is fake and doesn't want me around?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055952AAdkgCX</link><description>I don't know how to feel about her. We've been friends for almost a year now, she was like so nice at first, she would talk to me everyday, check on me, make sure to see if I was okay, call me , video chat with me, she even promised she'd always be here for me, like real friends do. Now let me tell you, we aren't the most popular kids around and she hasn't been acting herself lately, I feel almost as if she's trying to change herself to fit in with the crowd, I noticed she's been avoiding me lately, she always saying bye and saying she has to go somewhere when ik for sure  that isn't true because she didn't leave this much when we use to be close. I asked her why she always leaving and she said because she wanted to hang with her other friends, that 'we aren't that close" and she doesn't want to talk to me . That really pissed me off because I was like her FIRST friend, i helped her with so many things , I always had her back through thick and thin and all of sudden were not close?? I soon found out that she has a boyfriend, she's been making excuses and saying that she can't talk to me because she's on the phone with her boyfriend or that she's going to see a movie with her boyfriend which  I feel is total lie. I get that she may be busy, but I don't think she's that busy to the point we only talk for 10 seconds now. What do I do?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718055952AAdkgCX</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 06:59:52 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Why do they Make Porn?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060000AAnqUUF</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060000AAnqUUF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Maintenance &amp; Repairs ] Open Question : Radiator hose hot suspicious leaking?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060023AAbfOtd</link><description>Radiator is having behavior problems with this texas 100 degree heat.First yesterday i found there to be barely any coolant and the worst part was the over flow resevoire was extremely bad spraying anti freeze all over the battery. the level on the reservoir read (MIN).Today i drove it and it was spraying pretty damn bad but tonight i put a ton of anti freeze and the spraying has stopped i have not drove the truck but let it idle and heat up and all seem fine BUT there is leaking from something the passenger tire was very wet and i felt around the radiator and the radiator has a very strong heat AROUND THE RADIATOR HOSE.I also discovered STEEL HOSE LINE PREETY WET AND NOT LEAKING BUT PREETY DAMN WET for me not driving it for a few days.and i think the steel hose goes to radiator.As far as the major leak from somewhere that leaks on my tire i cannot really pin point other thinking its either a hose or the radiator but the radiator doesn't have significant bleeding i men its wet but it stops making me think its my own mess from pouring the anti freeze.

OH WELL I GUESS IN THE MORNING I WILL FIND A PUDDLE.

Picture below shows steel hose thats not dripping but WET.(top hose) FOUND MAJOR LEAK went on tire on passenger side seems the resevoir hose to the radiator is disconnected pouring out much anti freeze.So i guess what happened was hose poured out my anti freeze and I'm not sure why yesterday anti freeze started spraying out like crazy maybe its because the radiator had no anti freeze while i was driving thus making engine extremely hot.Im lucky i didn't ruin anything but i will find out tomorrow i doubt any damage.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060023AAbfOtd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:00:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Religion &amp; Spirituality ] Open Question : Why did God resort to killing the Egyptian firstborn, but only the firstborn of Egypt (Exodus 12:29)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060119AADb3gV</link><description>(1) Since Pharaoh hardened his heart and refused to allow the Israelites to go out of Egypt - He ignored God's every warning to let his people go out of Egypt in regards to the previous 9 plagues (Exodus 7-12).

(2) God would be unjust if he had not punished the Egyptians in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22 - The doctrine of eye for eye is due process, which requires the punishment to fit the nature of the crime (Exodus 21:24).

(3) Although the Egyptians were all guilty of genocide (Exodus 12:29) God had no choice but to exercise restraint by killing only the firstborn of Egypt - Which was due process in retaliation for the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22 - l'est all hell should break loose and Pharaoh would've lost any semblance of restraint in his dealings with the Israelites - So it was a matter of expedience that God was restrained in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22.


So, now do you see why God resorted to killing the Egyptian firstborn, whilst exercising restraint in response to the genocide of the Jews in Exodus 1:22?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060119AADb3gV</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:01:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : What are high heels good for?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060148AAdsQv3</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060148AAdsQv3</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:01:48 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Family ] Open Question : Hi everyone. So I turned 18 back in April (I'm a guy, by the way) and I still live at the house with my legal guardians (grandparents).?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060150AAxqQ4g</link><description>I'm going to college next month, but I've got issues here: a) They always complain about me not helping to pay for anything, yet they don't want me to have a job as they say I need to wait for my education to be finished first, b) They continue to try and force their Christianity on me when I've asked nicely for it to stop, and I've refused to participate in any church matters, and c) They promised me I would have my freedom when I turned 18, but here I stand today, still waiting for it. They want to control what music I listen to, what clothes I wear and when I wear them, where I go and when I go and who I go with. My parents are divorced and have other kids, and I can't stay with them, and can't afford to live on campus. So, my question is: What can I do? I'm losing my damn mind here!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060150AAxqQ4g</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:01:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Comics &amp; Animation ] Open Question : What anime series should I watch?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060309AARoMVm</link><description>I've seen Naruto (+Shipuudden), Code Geass, The Future Diary, Ergo Proxy, Bleach, Steins;Gate, One Punch Man, Sword Art Online, Boruto, My Hero Academia and Death Note. What would you think I would be interested in? Or you can introduce me to a series that you liked</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060309AARoMVm</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Newborn &amp; Baby ] Open Question : Why does Yahoo Answers select a default category for the questions?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060311AAA5iz5</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060311AAA5iz5</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:11 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ United States ] Open Question : How much can I make with a dependent in tax return while making $10000?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060320AAczlD4</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060320AAczlD4</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Diet &amp; Fitness ] Open Question : One side of my jaw is bigger than the other. Can i reduce it?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</link><description>I've noticed that my right jaw muscle is bigger than my left. Is there any way i can reduce it and even it out? I've been chewing on the left side of my mouth for months not but it hasn't been so effective.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: One side of my jaw is bigger than the other. Can i reduce it?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</link><description>I've noticed that my right jaw muscle is bigger than my left. Is there any way i can reduce it and even it out? I've been chewing on the left side of my mouth for months not but it hasn't been so effective.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060349AAwWHOa</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:03:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : GUYS: What do you find attractive in a girl?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060403AAjbKVK</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060403AAjbKVK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:04:03 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Friends ] Open Question : Does this mean he doesn't want me to have male friends?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060431AA91P4n</link><description>Does this mean he doesn't want me to have male friends? I was telling him about the girl who was mean to me at school I said "the teacher asked me a question and she (the girl) said 'you talk to him but not me?'" He said "who is him?" Him was the teacher. He never asks "who is her/she" when I mention female friends.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060431AA91P4n</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:04:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Other - Social Science ] Open Question : Are you happy with the way you look? why or why not?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AAbmLuw</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060455AAbmLuw</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:04:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Other - Cultures &amp; Groups ] Open Question : Do you consider a child with a Black mom and a dad that s mixed with White and Black (50/50) mixed?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060522AAsO9ey</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060522AAsO9ey</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Fashion &amp; Accessories ] Open Question : Best way to sale hundreds of used men's clothing items?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</link><description>T-shirts , jeans and shorts . They are like ten plus years old.

The clothing articles are too nice to just give away for free to the Goodwilll.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Best way to sale hundreds of used men's clothing items?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</link><description>T-shirts , jeans and shorts . They are like ten plus years old.

The clothing articles are too nice to just give away for free to the Goodwilll.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060529AAXOFqJ</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Do you think overweight people are ugly?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060534AAL6Zi9</link><description>Just wondering cause my friend's boyfriend just broke up with her and I asked him why and he said it was because she was fat. It really pissed me off, cause she is such an amazing person and they were together for 1 year too!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060534AAL6Zi9</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Wrestling ] Open Question : Will Jon ever come back?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</link><description>I just don't think he'll ever come back :(</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Will Jon ever come back?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</link><description>I just don't think he'll ever come back :(</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060541AAdNorF</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:41 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : If someone is afraid of losing a best friend, would that be a part of low self esteem?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060554AA1MAAl</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060554AA1MAAl</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Trivia ] Open Question : What's the worst insult you've ever received?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060558AAN61PH</link><description>by who?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060558AAN61PH</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:05:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Friends ] Open Question : I am 21 years old and I have social anxiety !?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060609AA0ekES</link><description>I have had anxiety really bad since I was a little kid. In elementary school, I was always sitting alone and I never had any friends. I have never been to a party in my life because it's hard for me to try to talk to new people and get to know people. Now that I am older, I know it is important to socialize with people for networking and things. I am a college student and I just don't know how to get over this anxiety that I have. Stepping out of my comfort zone has always scared me. Whenever someone wants to hang out with me , I would just not respond or just make up an excuse as to why I can't hang out with them... There are 2 people that I can hang out with that I do not have anxiety with but one of them has a boyfriend and the other is busy doing other things. We do hang out sometimes. It is just hard for me to get involved with the general public and socialize. I am afraid I'll have panic attacks and I get really offended easily by some people and the things they might say even if it's not meant to be offensive, I get very defensive. I would rather just stay in the house to myself without having to deal with the outside world. What should I do with myself?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060609AA0ekES</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Dream Interpretation ] Open Question : How can I stop myself from having these dreams?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060619AA4Mqys</link><description>This past year I've been having a similar stressful dream. I'm like flying through the universe and it just gets bigger and bigger. It's terrifying to me. And strange because the colors are so vivid and there is incredible detail in it. It scares me because I haven't seen these things before. I don't know how my brain is able to create such vivid scenery. It's so intense.

I want it to stop. What can I do?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060619AA4Mqys</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:19 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Law &amp; Ethics ] Open Question : Are you legally allowed to make pipe bombs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060635AANiz6w</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060635AANiz6w</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Corporations ] Open Question : Tell us 3 ways you will deliver world class service to our customers.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060651AAANiJu</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060651AAANiJu</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:51 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : What would you do if you woke up to this face?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060655AAQHhRI</link><description>https://s.yimg.com/tr/i/2e36dd47319d4e6f9bc2eb207ab33690_A.jpeg</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060655AAQHhRI</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Books &amp; Authors ] Open Question : Mystery story ideas?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</link><description>wow okay so i've been trying to create a detective webcomic with my friend since new years eve 2015

we haven't done anything for it since then because we could never come up with any ideas

we'd really appreciate some ideas, maybe abducting or homicide 

i dont know if this would help with anything, but its taking place in minneapolis, MN

 the two main characters are detective partners. ones a snarky 24 y/o vietnamese man and the other is an effeminate 23y/o american man and they're close childhood friends??????????

idk this might not be helpful but just in case.

10 points to best answer ;___;</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Mystery story ideas?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</link><description>wow okay so i've been trying to create a detective webcomic with my friend since new years eve 2015

we haven't done anything for it since then because we could never come up with any ideas

we'd really appreciate some ideas, maybe abducting or homicide 

i dont know if this would help with anything, but its taking place in minneapolis, MN

 the two main characters are detective partners. ones a snarky 24 y/o vietnamese man and the other is an effeminate 23y/o american man and they're close childhood friends??????????

idk this might not be helpful but just in case.

10 points to best answer ;___;</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060656AAKjAhg</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:06:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Fashion &amp; Accessories ] Open Question : Where can I find a Tron suit that lights up? I'm looking online and there's not many.. The ones that do are like $1600 can I find one?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060717AAzwtmb</link><description>Where can I find a Tron suit that lights up? I'm looking online and there's not many.. The ones that do are like $1600 can I find one?
Does anybody know of a place that sells them or where I can go? There's some for cheap like Walmart but they don't light up and to me that would be pointless. It doesn't have to be perfect just a standard suit that lights up. Does anyone know of a place that is a reasonable or where I could find a suit like that? I definitely don't want to pay that kind of money they're asking on eBay. Please help!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060717AAzwtmb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where can I find a Tron suit that lights up? I'm looking online and there's not many.. The ones that do are like $1600 can I find one?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060717AAzwtmb</link><description>Where can I find a Tron suit that lights up? I'm looking online and there's not many.. The ones that do are like $1600 can I find one?
Does anybody know of a place that sells them or where I can go? There's some for cheap like Walmart but they don't light up and to me that would be pointless. It doesn't have to be perfect just a standard suit that lights up. Does anyone know of a place that is a reasonable or where I could find a suit like that? I definitely don't want to pay that kind of money they're asking on eBay. Please help!</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060717AAzwtmb</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:07:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Diet &amp; Fitness ] Open Question : Water or apple cinder vinegar?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060749AAOuiSM</link><description>To help loose weight which do you think will be the most helpful? Water? or Apple cinder vinegar in water?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060749AAOuiSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Water or apple cinder vinegar?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060749AAOuiSM</link><description>To help loose weight which do you think will be the most helpful? Water? or Apple cinder vinegar in water?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060749AAOuiSM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:07:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Why does he keep telling me that?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060804AAi5GUD</link><description>So this guy and Ihave gotten very close these past 6 weeks, we attended a summer college get together and that's how we met. While we were at the college group camp we hun out a lot and talked every day about the camp and activities we did. It was so fun. He even paid for my ticket to go to schlitterbahn nad before I left camp he have made a huge box of goldfish (that's both our favorite snack). We've stayed in touch ever since. I even sent him a goldfish box in the mail to show how appreciative I was which he loved it! Although He keeps bringing this up.. he will say "everyone keeps saying your my girlfriend" or "Johnny just told asked me if your my girlfriend" or "my mom asked if it was my girlfriend who bought me the goldfish box and sent it in the mail" or "everyone thinks we're dating and that your my girlfriend" 
I just noticed he tells me that a lot, why? It's really no big deal</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060804AAi5GUD</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:04 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Politics ] Open Question : Did the GOPs KochCare ever intend to give better healthcare to America?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060817AALHxSV</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060817AALHxSV</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Do you know how to get rich by business?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060818AAWpe8t</link><description>I want to become a rich man by my self,but I don't know how to it in fact, do you know something about this?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060818AAWpe8t</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Basketball ] Open Question : Do you think Kawhi Leonard is a world-class NBA player??</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060834AAZ047K</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060834AAZ047K</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do you think Kawhi Leonard is a world-class NBA player??</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060834AAZ047K</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060834AAZ047K</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:34 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Mental Health ] Open Question : Bad sleeping issues?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060845AAUmgAd</link><description>i have extreme trouble when it comes to sleeping, i usually go to bed at 1 or 2 am and i wake up at 5 or 6. sometimes i see things, i know they are not real but they scare the hell out of me. If anyone has suggestions   on what is is wrong with me or have sleeping tips please tell me</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060845AAUmgAd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Bad sleeping issues?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060845AAUmgAd</link><description>i have extreme trouble when it comes to sleeping, i usually go to bed at 1 or 2 am and i wake up at 5 or 6. sometimes i see things, i know they are not real but they scare the hell out of me. If anyone has suggestions   on what is is wrong with me or have sleeping tips please tell me</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060845AAUmgAd</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Basketball ] Open Question : Do basketball players walk their own dogs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060858AAKE6zh</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060858AAKE6zh</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Do basketball players walk their own dogs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060858AAKE6zh</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060858AAKE6zh</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:08:58 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Friends ] Open Question : Why did he kee thanking me so much ?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060954AAbeNqM</link><description>So this guy and Ihave gotten very close these past 6 weeks, we attended a summer college get together and that's how we met. While we were at the college group camp we hun out a lot and talked every day about the camp and activities we did. It was so fun. He even paid for my ticket to go to schlitterbahn nad before I left camp he have made a huge box of goldfish (that's both our favorite snack). We've stayed in touch ever since. So as a thank you for what he did for me I sent him a giant box of goldfish in the mail, as something fun just to show how much I appreciated what he did. When he received it he messaged me saying how it meant so much to him, how he would write me a letter back and how it was the nicest thing anyone has ever done for him. All through out the day he just kept messaging me thanking me for it and how it meant so much,  Do you think he really meant that?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718060954AAbeNqM</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:09:54 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Other - Sports ] Open Question : How much do MASL soccer professional dancers/cheerleaders get paid?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061002AAsSt37</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061002AAsSt37</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How much do MASL soccer professional dancers/cheerleaders get paid?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061002AAsSt37</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061002AAsSt37</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:10:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Cooking &amp; Recipes ] Open Question : Do people really roast chestnuts over an open fire on Christmas just to throw them away to the birds the next morning?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061023AAsNRE6</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061023AAsNRE6</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Medicine ] Open Question : Can biogesic(paracetamol) kill u?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061040AA2PqlY</link><description>Okay so, im a grade 9 student. And since grade 7 i really want to commit suicide but I can t see any easy ways to die.  Just now I ve heard about overdose yourself on medecine. Dont say something like no dont kill urself remember u have a family blabla. I ve decided already. I only have biogesic here so i want to know how many tablets i need to gulped. And if it can really kill u. Its 500mg. PLEASE I NEED AN ANSWER . If u guys wanna know my age im 14</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061040AA2PqlY</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:10:40 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Other - Careers &amp; Employment ] Open Question : Quiting a job advise?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061115AA6yotn</link><description>So I started a apprentiship for machining and thought that I would really enjoy it. After working for about 4 months I came to realize that I really do not like it and I want out. My boss thinks that after I finish my first class I'm going to continue on learning for 4 more years and working there long term. I decided I want to quit because of so many reasons I can't even count. I don't fit in with the machinest environment, unhealthy and unsafe ect. What is the best way to tell my boss this, I feel like he will be disappointed that he took me in the first place. I know for sure almost this is not what I want to do so I'm not planning on just sticking through it my whole life.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061115AA6yotn</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Computer Networking ] Open Question : "Unidentified network"?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061127AAitQqX</link><description>I am using my old laptop as a router for my PC. All is working fine until I updated Windows in my laptop. In my desktop, it shows the ethernet symbol with an exclamation mark with it. It says it s an unidentified network.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061127AAitQqX</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:27 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Can anyone please be my girlfriend? Urgent!?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061128AAWcTNR</link><description>27 and still nothing</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061128AAWcTNR</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Singles &amp; Dating ] Open Question : Does the car wash boy want me to look for him?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061149AAjuVBU</link><description>This question is for psychics, if there are any available.  (All the "free" psychic chats I've found end up charging you).

I want to know if the young cute sexy guy with the long curly blond hair who was nice to me at the car wash when I was 3 wants me to look for him or not.  I just want to know if I'm imagining the connection I think I still  have with him.  Trolls, don't bother, as I will ask you to provide a description of how I look, that way I know you are truly psychic, thx.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061149AAjuVBU</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:49 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Yahoo Answers ] Open Question : What are the Yahoo Answers' terms of service?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061155AAl0NRV</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061155AAl0NRV</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Polls &amp; Surveys ] Open Question : Can you do any accents?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061156AAseUV0</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061156AAseUV0</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:11:56 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Politics ] Open Question : About those Russian sanctions ... shouldn't they be increased in harshness due to the blatant interfering by Russia in the 2016 US election?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061209AAQ5CIK</link><description>Get other western nations on board as well, undermining western democratic nations is not in our interest  ... send a clear message to Putin that his games are not welcome.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061209AAQ5CIK</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:12:09 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ Primary &amp; Secondary Education ] Open Question : Should I stay or move to a new state to finish my senior year of high school?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061210AAP0NKx</link><description>I'm currently trying to decide on whether to move to a new state, or stay at my home state for my senior year of high school. At home, I have all my friends, I know the school and everyone in it, and I know the place. However, my family there ain't the greatest to me. My mom and sister both gang up on me and the whole situation there isn't the greatest. In the state I'm thinking of moving to, I know no one but my dads girlfriend and her kids. I don't know the area all that well, I've visited the school that I would be going to if I did stay and kind of like it, the teachers at my other school sucked, I feel slightly more comfortable here than at my home state because I'm not being attacked by my family 24/7, but all of my really close friends are back at home.I don't know what to decide. All of my close friends are saying that they'll support my decision. Is there anything that can help make my decision easier or have any advice for me?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170718061210AAP0NKx</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 07:12:10 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>[ LiveQA2017_Medical_Subtask] FakeMedical Question 1</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=MEDQid1</link><description>NLM FAQ questions for TREC LiveQA 2017 </description><guid isPermaLink="true">https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=MEDQid1</guid><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2017 19:44:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: My daughter is 8 years old and is wanting to dress as Harley Quinn for her jazz solo. What would be a good upbeat song for her to dance to?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004842AAEZArt</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707004842AAEZArt</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:48:42 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Are there any Allpoint ATM machines in Kansas City that accept deposits?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005118AAVcg4S</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005118AAVcg4S</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:51:18 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Should hitting an ace in a tennis match result in automatic victory?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005129AAcvCpf</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005129AAcvCpf</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:51:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Uncontrollable body odor. help!! effecting life. (suicidal)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011228AA6WW1t</link><description>long story short I am a dancer. I never had this problem up until about 2 years ago(I m 20 yr old male now) . 
its really not a problem until I start to sweat extremely-in long tense rehearsals that last for more than 2 hrs.
p.s I been through puberty. 12

I understand its the bacteria that comes in when the skin is soaked with sweat which makes sense because after I stop activity for a bit I smell fine including the clothes I take off.

my daily routine ever since this problem: at night I wash (dove soap), put clinical deodorant (dove) on I wake up stretch( in which I sweat get in the shower and put good quality deodorant on (dove). I tried different deodorants that are not like powder doesn t work for me

this caused so much stress on my life I literally had suicidal thoughts cause of some of the bullying. I became a vegetarian for several months. and recently I stopped eating sugar for days. because it came out of no where. I m seeing a doctor soon I honestly feel helpless and I just don t know... my life is dark rn.
can any of you help? products? doing something wrong? Is there a way I can lessen the bacteria and or sweat. I don t want to lose opportunities because of this</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011228AA6WW1t</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:12:28 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Have you read Les Miserables or Moby Dick? Which is better?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011236AA2XuMx</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011236AA2XuMx</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:12:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Which verse is more better for my poetry:)?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011805AAS4grK</link><description>The villagers gathered round in horror and disbelief,half a body washed up upon the shore.
or 
The villagers gathered round in horror and disbelief,half a body washed upon the shore.
or
The villagers gathered round in horror and disbelief,half a body washed up on the shore.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011805AAS4grK</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:18:05 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Who can I call SAW to get stray kittens out of my yard tonight?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010826AACW0kT</link><description>All if the local shelters are closed as well as the humane society, but there are 3 kittens in my backyard that I need to get rid of asap as my boyfriend is allergic. Who can I call to pick them up after hours? Or will I have to wait until tomorrow?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010826AACW0kT</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:08:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Can I join softball? I'm 13.?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011735AAR5MhZ</link><description>I'm 13 and I think I want to try out for softball. I'll be going into highschool next year. I am completely a beginner, never played before. If I joined I'm not sure if I'll be taught all the way from the beginning while others are more experienced than me.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011735AAR5MhZ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:17:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Catching a horse by raising your arm up?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011023AAe5HeA</link><description>I was at a horse event today and one of the things competitors did was unhalter their horse and soon after go catch them again. A few called the horse to them by raising their arm over their head, and I was wondering if this was a certain method they were following; parelli, clinton anderson, etc.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707011023AAe5HeA</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:10:23 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do i grow a rose bush from cuttings?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706141645AAVjhzy</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706141645AAVjhzy</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 15:16:45 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Is my 200m time good?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005208AA3SzRQ</link><description>This was my FIRST year in track and I m 13 years old so my times might not be too good. For 200m my best was 27.4sec and for 100m my best is 12.9sec. I personally think I have all the speed necessary to get better but I need to perfect my form for both 100 and 200. I qualified for the Meet of Champions for both 100 and 200 and I was the anchor for the relay team. So what do you think about my times? How should I improve? I know I have the speed, i just need to improve endurance and form, how CAN I DO THAT??</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005208AA3SzRQ</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:52:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: How do actors/actresses memorize their lines?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005722AAAmK8g</link><description>I just want to know how they memorize their lines. Do they memorize the entire script or do they memorize a few lines for a certain scene and then so on and so on</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005722AAAmK8g</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:57:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What is the difference or description of natural ornamental plants and artificial ornamental plants?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706142257AArzOwV</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706142257AArzOwV</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 15:22:57 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Game of thrones characters who have not killed anybody?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005753AAmhcob</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707005753AAmhcob</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 01:57:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Looking for really wide office chairs/ pet friendly chairs?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706141150AAyk8ID</link><description>I'm trying to find an office chair that is extra wide. I have a dog (a whippet) that likes  to sit in my lap, but there isn't enough space between the arm rests. It doesn't have to be an office chair, but I would prefer it. Maybe something like what's in this picture, except not a bench. Or a rocking chair.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706141150AAyk8ID</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 15:11:50 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Where can i legally spray paint my things?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706082755AAmcQ98</link><description>I am not asking for graffiti related tips. I want to spray paint some of my own property. I live in an apartment so I can t do it here.</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706082755AAmcQ98</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 09:27:55 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: What should I use to clean a new letter box?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706140236AAJPuNm</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706140236AAJPuNm</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 15:02:36 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Help with mojo bags?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706105730AAz4EP8</link><description>Im doing a mojo bag for protection or spell banishing (not yet sure what to do because ingredients are hard to find) and im not sure if i should use not fresh or dried herbs or fresh herbs freshly picked from a garden or something. Since i can't find any stone or crystals, i just bought herbs, and i only have two kinds of herbs. Is it enough to just use two? And should i use fresh herbs or is it fine if i use dried ones. Thank you</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706105730AAz4EP8</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 11:57:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Tru-test deluxe 32 inch cut riding lawn mowers from the 50?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153208AAOMSjH</link><description>I got this TRU-TEST DELUXE 32 inch cut riding lawn mower and I'm not sure what year it was made but I have the book for it and it still runs here are the serial number 2-832E3-1754  is it last four number that tell when it was made?</description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170706153208AAOMSjH</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 16:32:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Question: Why are we trapped in our bodies during abuse?</title><link>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010817AATQk7S</link><description></description><guid>https://answers.yahoo.com/question/index?qid=20170707010817AATQk7S</guid><pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2017 02:08:17 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>